<row Id="123" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="183" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:08:52.353" Score="72" ViewCount="58655" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there an existing application or library in &lt;em&gt;Java&lt;/em&gt; which will allow me to convert a &lt;code&gt;CSV&lt;/code&gt; data file to &lt;code&gt;XML&lt;/code&gt; file?  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;XML&lt;/code&gt; tags would be provided through possibly the first row containing column headings.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="78" LastEditorUserId="2553431" LastEditorDisplayName="Jeff Atwood" LastEditDate="2015-10-27T09:34:09.503" LastActivityDate="2016-04-10T20:56:11.613" Title="Java lib or app to convert CSV to XML file?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;xml&gt;&lt;csv&gt;&lt;data-conversion&gt;" AnswerCount="16" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="17" />
<row Id="126" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="127" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:10:30.337" Score="63" ViewCount="8274" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the &quot;purist&quot; or &quot;correct&quot; way to access an object's properties from within an object method that is not a getter/setter method?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know that from outside of the object you should use a getter/setter, but from within would you just do:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String property = this.property;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PHP:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$property = $this-&amp;gt;property;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;or would you do:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String property = this.getProperty();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PHP:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$property = $this-&amp;gt;getProperty();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Forgive me if my Java is a little off, it's been a year since I programmed in Java...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems people are assuming I am talking about private or protected variables/properties only. When I learned OO I was taught to use getters/setters for every single property even if it was public (and actually I was told never to make any variable/property public). So, I may be starting off from a false assumption from the get go. It appears that people answering this question are maybe saying that you should have public properties and that those don't need getters and setters, which goes against what I was taught, and what I was talking about, although maybe that needs to be discussed as well. That's probably a good topic for a different question though...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58" LastEditorUserId="202431" LastEditorDisplayName="Gaius" LastEditDate="2010-01-20T08:27:13.130" LastActivityDate="2015-11-15T17:36:30.327" Title="How would you access Object properties from within an object method?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;php&gt;&lt;oop&gt;&lt;theory&gt;" AnswerCount="18" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2012-05-08T18:11:27.270" />
<row Id="127" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:13:47.600" Score="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;This has religious war potential, but it seems to me that if you're using a getter/setter, you should use it internally as well - using both will lead to maintenance problems down the road (e.g. somebody adds code to a setter that &lt;em&gt;needs&lt;/em&gt; to run every time that property is set, and the property is being set internally w/o that setter being called).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="35" LastEditorUserId="35" LastEditorDisplayName="Greg" LastEditDate="2008-08-01T16:32:17.110" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T16:32:17.110" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="128" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:19:04.283" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;It depends on how the property is used. For example, say you have a student object that has a name property. You could use your Get method to pull the name from the database, if it hasn't been retrieved already. This way you are reducing unnecessary calls to the database.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now let's say you have a private integer counter in your object that counts the number of times the name has been called. You may want to not use the Get method from inside the object because it would produce an invalid count.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="26" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T16:19:04.283" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="133" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:31:43.430" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This may be too basic or limited of a solution, but couldn't you do a &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/7/docs/api/java/lang/String.html#split(java.lang.String)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;String.split()&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on each line of the file, remembering the result array of the first line to generate the XML, and just spit each line's array data out with the proper XML elements padding each iteration of a loop?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="59" LastEditorUserId="1102512" LastEditDate="2013-11-26T00:02:16.310" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T00:02:16.310" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="139" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:43:30.880" Score="10" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Am I just going overboard here?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps ;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another approach would be to utilize a private/protected method to actually do the getting (caching/db/etc), and a public wrapper for it that increments the count:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PHP:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public function getName() {&#xA;    $this-&amp;gt;incrementNameCalled();&#xA;    return $this-&amp;gt;_getName();&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;protected function _getName() {&#xA;    return $this-&amp;gt;name;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;and then from within the object itself:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PHP:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;$name = $this-&amp;gt;_getName();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This way you can still use that first argument for something else (like sending a flag for whether or not to used cached data here perhaps).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="72" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T16:43:30.880" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="142" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T16:56:55.830" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, it seems with C# 3.0 properties' default implementation, the decision is taken for you; you HAVE to set the property using the (possibly private) property setter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I personally only use the private member-behind when not doing so would cause the object to fall in an less than desirable state, such as when initializing or when caching/lazy loading is involved.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="42" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T16:56:55.830" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="143" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T17:01:27.240" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;As stated in some of the comments: Sometimes you should, sometimes you shouldn't. The great part about private variables is that you are able to see all the places they are used when you change something. If your getter/setter does something you need, use it. If it doesn't matter you decide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The opposite case could be made that if you use the getter/setter and somebody changes the getter/setter they have to analyze all the places the getter and setter is used internally to see if it messes something up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="86" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T17:01:27.240" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="169" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-01T18:23:59.040" Score="38" Body="&lt;p&gt;Personally, I feel like it's important to remain consistent.  If you have getters and setters, use them.  The only time I would access a field directly is when the accessor has a lot of overhead.  It may feel like you're bloating your code unnecessarily, but it can certainly save a whole lot of headache in the future.  The classic example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Later on, you may desire to change the way that field works.  Maybe it should be calculated on-the-fly or maybe you would like to use a different type for the backing store.  If you are accessing properties directly, a change like that can break an awful lot of code in one swell foop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="93" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T18:23:59.040" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="183" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-01T18:51:12.090" Score="51" Body="&lt;p&gt;Maybe this might help: &lt;a href=&quot;http://jsefa.sourceforge.net/quick-tutorial.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JSefa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can read CSV file with this tool and serialize it to XML.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="86" LastEditorUserId="395659" LastEditDate="2013-02-07T10:36:04.283" LastActivityDate="2013-02-07T10:36:04.283" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="190" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-01T19:21:57.517" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't understand why you would want to do this. It sounds almost like cargo cult coding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Converting a CSV file to XML doesn't add any value. Your program is already reading the CSV file, so arguing that you need XML doesn't work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, reading the CSV file, doing &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; with the values, and then serializing to XML does make sense (well, as much as using XML can make sense... ;)) but you would supposedly already have a means of serializing to XML.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="55" LastActivityDate="2008-08-01T19:21:57.517" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="382" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="384" CreationDate="2008-08-02T08:58:27.540" Score="41" ViewCount="7767" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the meaning of the &lt;em&gt;Java warning&lt;/em&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Type safety: The cast from Object to List is actually checking against the erased type List&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I get this warning when I try to cast an Object to a type with generic information, such as in the following code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Object object = getMyList();&#xA;List&amp;lt;Integer&amp;gt; list = (List&amp;lt;Integer&amp;gt;) object;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditorUserId="3787519" LastEditDate="2015-12-29T06:32:00.833" LastActivityDate="2015-12-29T06:32:32.877" Title="What is the meaning of the type safety warning in certain Java generics casts?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;generics&gt;&lt;warnings&gt;&lt;casting&gt;&lt;type-safety&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="6" />
<row Id="384" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="382" CreationDate="2008-08-02T08:58:48.430" Score="39" Body="&lt;p&gt;This warning is there because Java is not actually storing type information at run-time in an object that uses generics.  Thus, if &lt;code&gt;object&lt;/code&gt; is actually a &lt;code&gt;List&amp;lt;String&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;, there will be no &lt;code&gt;ClassCastException&lt;/code&gt; at run-time except until an item is accessed from the list that doesn't match the generic type defined in the variable.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This can cause further complications if items are added to the list, with this incorrect generic type information.  Any code still holding a reference to the list but with the correct generic type information will now have an inconsistent list.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To remove the warning, try:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;List&amp;lt;?&amp;gt; list = (List&amp;lt;?&amp;gt;) object;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, note that you will not be able to use certain methods such as add because the compiler doesn't know if you are trying to add an object of incorrect type.  The above will work in a lot of situations, but if you have to use add, or some similarly restricted method, you will just have to suffer the yellow underline in Eclipse (or a &lt;code&gt;SuppressWarning&lt;/code&gt; annotation).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditorUserId="3787519" LastEditDate="2015-12-29T06:32:32.877" LastActivityDate="2015-12-29T06:32:32.877" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="540" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-02T19:06:38.717" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;As far as I know, there's no ready-made library to do this for you, but producing a tool capable of translating from CSV to XML should only require you to write a crude CSV parser and hook up JDOM (or your XML Java library of choice) with some glue code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="154" LastEditorUserId="1564659" LastEditDate="2016-04-10T20:56:11.613" LastActivityDate="2016-04-10T20:56:11.613" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="564" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="566" CreationDate="2008-08-02T21:47:34.820" Score="169" ViewCount="156162" Body="&lt;p&gt;I was reading &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/1430209879&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;More Joel on Software&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; when I came across &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joel_Spolsky&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Joel Spolsky&lt;/a&gt; saying something about a particular type of programmer knowing the difference between an &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt; and an &lt;code&gt;Integer&lt;/code&gt; in Java/C# (Object Oriented Programming Languages).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what is the difference?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastEditorUserId="1788806" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Reath" LastEditDate="2016-09-23T14:50:20.907" LastActivityDate="2016-09-23T14:50:20.907" Title="What is the difference between an int and an Integer in Java and C#?" Tags="&lt;c#&gt;&lt;java&gt;&lt;integer&gt;&lt;int&gt;" AnswerCount="19" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="45" />
<row Id="566" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-02T21:55:45.477" Score="163" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In Java,&lt;/strong&gt; the 'int' type is a primitive , whereas the 'Integer' type is an object.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In C#,&lt;/strong&gt; the 'int' type is the same as &lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt; and is &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/s1ax56ch.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;a value type&lt;/a&gt; (ie more like the java 'int'). An integer (just like any other value types) can be &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/yz2be5wk.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;boxed&lt;/a&gt; (&quot;wrapped&quot;) into an object. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The differences between objects and primitives are somewhat beyond the scope of this question, but to summarize: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objects&lt;/strong&gt; provide facilities for polymorphism, are passed by reference (or more accurately have references passed by value), and are allocated from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dynamic_memory_allocation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;heap&lt;/a&gt;. Conversely, &lt;strong&gt;primitives&lt;/strong&gt; are immutable types that are passed by value and are often allocated from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stack-based_memory_allocation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="154" LastEditorUserId="8521" LastEditorDisplayName="Matt" LastEditDate="2013-09-24T09:16:45.727" LastActivityDate="2013-09-24T09:16:45.727" CommentCount="9" />
<row Id="568" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-02T22:05:08.093" Score="115" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, in Java an int is a primitive while an Integer is an Object. Meaning, if you made a new Integer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer i = new Integer(6);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You could call some method on i:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String s = i.toString();//sets s the string representation of i&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whereas with an int:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int i = 6;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You cannot call any methods on it, because it is simply a primitive. So:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String s = i.toString();//will not work!!!&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;would produce an error, because int is not an object.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;int is one of the few primitives in Java (along with char and some others). I'm not 100% sure, but I'm thinking that the Integer object more or less just has an int property and a whole bunch of methods to interact with that property (like the toString() method for example). So Integer is a fancy way to work with an int (Just as perhaps String is a fancy way to work with a group of chars).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I know that Java isn't C, but since I've never programmed in C this is the closest I could come to the answer. Hope this helps!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/lang/Integer.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Integer object javadoc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mindprod.com/jgloss/intvsinteger.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Integer Ojbect vs. int primitive comparison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58" LastEditorUserId="1102512" LastEditDate="2013-11-26T00:10:45.857" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T00:10:45.857" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="583" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-02T23:37:10.077" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;In C#, int is just an &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;alias&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for &lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt;, string for &lt;code&gt;System.String&lt;/code&gt;, double for &lt;code&gt;System.Double&lt;/code&gt; etc...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personally I prefer int, string, double, etc. because they don't require a &lt;code&gt;using System;&lt;/code&gt; statement :) A silly reason, I know...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39" LastEditorUserId="2935678" LastEditorDisplayName="huseyint" LastEditDate="2014-06-05T10:12:06.170" LastActivityDate="2014-06-05T10:12:06.170" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="608" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-03T02:32:50.690" Score="27" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll add to the excellent answers given above, and talk about boxing and unboxing, and how this applies to Java (although C# has it too). I'll use just Java terminology, because I am more &lt;em&gt;au fait&lt;/em&gt; with that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As the answers mentioned, &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt; is just a number (called the &lt;em&gt;unboxed&lt;/em&gt; type), whereas &lt;code&gt;Integer&lt;/code&gt; is an object (which contains the number, hence a &lt;em&gt;boxed&lt;/em&gt; type). In Java terms, that means (apart from not being able to call methods on &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt;), you cannot store &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt; or other non-object types in collections (&lt;code&gt;List&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;Map&lt;/code&gt;, etc.). In order to store them, you must first box them up in its corresponding boxed type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 5 onwards have something called &lt;em&gt;auto-boxing&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;auto-unboxing&lt;/em&gt; which allow the boxing/unboxing to be done behind the scenes. Compare and contrast: Java 5 version:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Deque&amp;lt;Integer&amp;gt; queue;&#xA;&#xA;void add(int n) {&#xA;    queue.add(n);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;int remove() {&#xA;    return queue.remove();&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java 1.4 or earlier (no generics either):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Deque queue;&#xA;&#xA;void add(int n) {&#xA;    queue.add(Integer.valueOf(n));&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;int remove() {&#xA;    return ((Integer) queue.remove()).intValue();&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It must be noted that despite the brevity in the Java 5 version, both versions generate identical bytecode. Thus, although auto-boxing and auto-unboxing is very convenient because you write less code, these operations &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; happen behind the scenes, with the same runtime costs, so you still have to be aware of their existence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hope this helps!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="13" LastEditorUserId="13" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Jester-Young" LastEditDate="2008-08-03T05:10:24.710" LastActivityDate="2008-08-03T05:10:24.710" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="939" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-04T01:07:07.633" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is nothing I know of that can do this without you at least writing a little bit of code... You will need 2 separate library:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A CSV Parser Framework &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;An XML Serialization Framework&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CSV parser I would recommend (unless you want to have a little bit of fun to write your own CSV Parser) is OpenCSV (A SourceForge Project for parsing CSV Data)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The XML Serialization Framework should be something that can scale in case you want to transform large (or huge) CSV file to XML: My recommendation is the Sun Java Streaming XML Parser Framework (See &lt;a href=&quot;https://sjsxp.java.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) which allows pull-parsing AND serialization.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="244" LastEditorUserId="1102512" LastEditDate="2013-11-26T00:02:54.033" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T00:02:54.033" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="1266" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-04T14:11:03.557" Score="21" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'll just post here since some of the other posts are slightly inaccurate in relation to C#.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correct:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt; is an alias for &lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Wrong:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;float&lt;/code&gt; is not an alias for &lt;code&gt;System.Float&lt;/code&gt;, but for &lt;code&gt;System.Single&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Basically, int is a reserved keyword in the C# programming language, and is an alias for the &lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt; value type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;float and Float is not the same however, as the right system type for ''&lt;code&gt;float&lt;/code&gt;'' is System.Single. There are some types like this that has reserved keywords that doesn't seem to match the type names directly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In C# there is no difference between ''&lt;code&gt;int&lt;/code&gt;'' and ''&lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt;'', or any of the other pairs or keywords/system types, except for when defining enums. With enums you can specify the storage size to use and in this case you can only use the reserved keyword, and not the system runtime type name.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wether the value in the int will be stored on the stack, in memory, or as a referenced heap object depends on the context and how you use it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This declaration in a method:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int i;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;defines a variable &lt;code&gt;i&lt;/code&gt; of type &lt;code&gt;System.Int32&lt;/code&gt;, living in a register or on the stack, depending on optimizations. The same declaration in a type (struct or class) defines a member field. The same declaration in a method argument list defines a parameter, with the same storage options as for a local variable. (note that this paragraph is not valid if you start pulling iterator methods into the mix, these are different beasts altogether)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To get a heap object, you can use boxing:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;object o = i;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;this will create a boxed copy of the contents of &lt;code&gt;i&lt;/code&gt; on the heap. In IL you can access methods on the heap object directly, but in C# you need to cast it back to an int, which will create another copy. Thus, the object on the heap cannot easily be changed in C# without creating a new boxed copy of a new int value. (Ugh, this paragraph doesn't read all that easily.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="267" LastEditorUserId="4551041" LastEditDate="2015-11-30T15:31:10.063" LastActivityDate="2015-11-30T15:31:10.063" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="1582" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-04T21:02:54.910" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;This has already been answered for Java, here's the C# answer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&quot;Integer&quot; is not a valid type name in C# and &quot;int&quot; is just an alias for System.Int32. Also, unlike in Java (or C++) there aren't any special primitive types in C#, every instance of a type in C# (including int) is an object. Here's some demonstrative code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;void DoStuff()&#xA;{&#xA;    System.Console.WriteLine( SomeMethod((int)5) );&#xA;    System.Console.WriteLine( GetTypeName&amp;lt;int&amp;gt;() );&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;string SomeMethod(object someParameter)&#xA;{&#xA;    return string.Format(&quot;Some text {0}&quot;, someParameter.ToString());&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;string GetTypeName&amp;lt;T&amp;gt;()&#xA;{&#xA;    return (typeof (T)).FullName;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="332" LastActivityDate="2008-08-04T21:02:54.910" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="2092" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-05T11:15:16.953" Score="15" ViewCount="1702" Body="&lt;p&gt;Looking for books or other references that discuss actually &lt;em&gt;&quot;how&quot;&lt;/em&gt; to write a code coverage tool in Java; some of the various techniques or tricks - source vs. byte code instrumentation. This is for a scripting language that generates java byte code under the hood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="bill" LastEditorUserId="2833965" LastEditorDisplayName="Ned Batchelder" LastEditDate="2015-12-15T05:55:55.830" LastActivityDate="2016-10-13T12:50:44.040" Title="How to get started &quot;writing&quot; a code coverage tool?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;testing&gt;&lt;coldfusion&gt;&lt;code-coverage&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2158" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="2245" CreationDate="2008-08-05T12:15:08.283" Score="70" ViewCount="79807" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there a way to create a &lt;code&gt;JButton&lt;/code&gt; with your own button graphic and not just with an image inside the button? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If not, is there another way to create a custom button in java?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="340" LastEditorUserId="126039" LastEditDate="2016-06-15T08:02:32.130" LastActivityDate="2016-10-27T07:19:59.620" Title="Creating a custom button in Java" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;swing&gt;&lt;jbutton&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="31" />
<row Id="2181" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2158" CreationDate="2008-08-05T12:30:34.757" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I haven't done SWING development since my early CS classes but if it wasn't built in you could just inherit javax.swing.AbstractButton and create your own. Should be pretty simple to wire something together with their existing framework.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="200" LastActivityDate="2008-08-05T12:30:34.757" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2210" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2158" CreationDate="2008-08-05T12:47:17.967" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;You could always try the Synth look &amp;amp; feel. You provide an xml file that acts as a sort of stylesheet, along with any images you want to use. The code might look like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;try {&#xA;    SynthLookAndFeel synth = new SynthLookAndFeel();&#xA;    Class aClass = MainFrame.class;&#xA;    InputStream stream = aClass.getResourceAsStream(&quot;\\default.xml&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;    if (stream == null) {&#xA;        System.err.println(&quot;Missing configuration file&quot;);&#xA;        System.exit(-1);                &#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    synth.load(stream, aClass);&#xA;&#xA;    UIManager.setLookAndFeel(synth);&#xA;} catch (ParseException pe) {&#xA;    System.err.println(&quot;Bad configuration file&quot;);&#xA;    pe.printStackTrace();&#xA;    System.exit(-2);&#xA;} catch (UnsupportedLookAndFeelException ulfe) {&#xA;    System.err.println(&quot;Old JRE in use. Get a new one&quot;);&#xA;    System.exit(-3);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From there, go on and add your JButton like you normally would. The only change is that you use the setName(string) method to identify what the button should map to in the xml file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The xml file might look like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;synth&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;style id=&quot;button&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;font name=&quot;DIALOG&quot; size=&quot;12&quot; style=&quot;BOLD&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;state value=&quot;MOUSE_OVER&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;imagePainter method=&quot;buttonBackground&quot; path=&quot;dirt.png&quot; sourceInsets=&quot;2 2 2 2&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;insets top=&quot;2&quot; botton=&quot;2&quot; right=&quot;2&quot; left=&quot;2&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/state&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;state value=&quot;ENABLED&quot;&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;imagePainter method=&quot;buttonBackground&quot; path=&quot;dirt.png&quot; sourceInsets=&quot;2 2 2 2&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;            &amp;lt;insets top=&quot;2&quot; botton=&quot;2&quot; right=&quot;2&quot; left=&quot;2&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;        &amp;lt;/state&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;/style&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;bind style=&quot;button&quot; type=&quot;name&quot; key=&quot;dirt&quot;/&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/synth&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The bind element there specifies what to map to (in this example, it will apply that styling to any buttons whose name property has been set to &quot;dirt&quot;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And a couple of useful links:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://javadesktop.org/articles/synth/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://javadesktop.org/articles/synth/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/uiswing/lookandfeel/synth.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/tutorial/uiswing/lookandfeel/synth.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="246" LastEditorUserId="1795426" LastEditorDisplayName="rjohnston" LastEditDate="2014-09-22T17:28:03.387" LastActivityDate="2014-09-22T17:28:03.387" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2216" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2092" CreationDate="2008-08-05T12:50:59.020" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Thxm, Mc! &lt;a href=&quot;http://asm.objectweb.org&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://asm.objectweb.org&lt;/a&gt;/ is another one. &lt;em&gt;Excellent&lt;/em&gt; documentation on byte code instrumentation, but nothing &quot;directly&quot; aimed at writing a coverage tool - just some hints or ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="bill" LastEditorUserId="1571180" LastEditDate="2016-10-13T12:50:44.040" LastActivityDate="2016-10-13T12:50:44.040" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2225" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2158" CreationDate="2008-08-05T12:53:35.990" Score="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes, this is possible. One of the main pros for using Swing is the ease with which the abstract controls can be created and manipulates.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is a quick and dirty way to extend the existing JButton class to draw a circle to the right of the text.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;package test;&#xA;&#xA;import java.awt.Color;&#xA;import java.awt.Container;&#xA;import java.awt.Dimension;&#xA;import java.awt.FlowLayout;&#xA;import java.awt.Graphics;&#xA;&#xA;import javax.swing.JButton;&#xA;import javax.swing.JFrame;&#xA;&#xA;public class MyButton extends JButton {&#xA;&#xA;    private static final long serialVersionUID = 1L;&#xA;&#xA;    private Color circleColor = Color.BLACK;&#xA;&#xA;    public MyButton(String label) {&#xA;        super(label);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @Override&#xA;    protected void paintComponent(Graphics g) {&#xA;        super.paintComponent(g);&#xA;&#xA;        Dimension originalSize = super.getPreferredSize();&#xA;        int gap = (int) (originalSize.height * 0.2);&#xA;        int x = originalSize.width + gap;&#xA;        int y = gap;&#xA;        int diameter = originalSize.height - (gap * 2);&#xA;&#xA;        g.setColor(circleColor);&#xA;        g.fillOval(x, y, diameter, diameter);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    @Override&#xA;    public Dimension getPreferredSize() {&#xA;        Dimension size = super.getPreferredSize();&#xA;        size.width += size.height;&#xA;        return size;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    /*Test the button*/&#xA;    public static void main(String[] args) {&#xA;        MyButton button = new MyButton(&quot;Hello, World!&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;        JFrame frame = new JFrame();&#xA;        frame.setDefaultCloseOperation(JFrame.EXIT_ON_CLOSE);&#xA;        frame.setSize(400, 400);&#xA;&#xA;        Container contentPane = frame.getContentPane();&#xA;        contentPane.setLayout(new FlowLayout());&#xA;        contentPane.add(button);&#xA;&#xA;        frame.setVisible(true);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note that by overriding &lt;strong&gt;paintComponent&lt;/strong&gt; that the contents of the button can be changed, but that the border is painted by the &lt;strong&gt;paintBorder&lt;/strong&gt; method. The &lt;strong&gt;getPreferredSize&lt;/strong&gt; method also needs to be managed in order to dynamically support changes to the content. Care needs to be taken when measuring font metrics and image dimensions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For creating a control that you can rely on, the above code is not the correct approach. Dimensions and colours are dynamic in Swing and are dependent on the look and feel being used. Even the default &lt;em&gt;Metal&lt;/em&gt; look has changed across JRE versions. It would be better to implement &lt;strong&gt;AbstractButton&lt;/strong&gt; and conform to the guidelines set out by the Swing API. A good starting point is to look at the &lt;strong&gt;javax.swing.LookAndFeel&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;javax.swing.UIManager&lt;/strong&gt; classes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/8/docs/api/javax/swing/LookAndFeel.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/8/docs/api/javax/swing/LookAndFeel.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/8/docs/api/javax/swing/UIManager.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/8/docs/api/javax/swing/UIManager.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Understanding the anatomy of LookAndFeel is useful for writing controls:&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wayback.archive.org/web/20090309070901/http://java.sun.com/products/jfc/tsc/articles/sce/index.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Creating a Custom Look and Feel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="304" LastEditorUserId="1795426" LastEditDate="2014-09-22T17:33:24.200" LastActivityDate="2014-09-22T17:33:24.200" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2245" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2158" CreationDate="2008-08-05T13:03:43.707" Score="77" Body="&lt;p&gt;When I was first learning Java we had to make Yahtzee and I thought it would be cool to create custom Swing components and containers instead of just drawing everything on one &lt;code&gt;JPanel&lt;/code&gt;.  The benefit of extending &lt;code&gt;Swing&lt;/code&gt; components, of course, is to have the ability to add support for keyboard shortcuts and other accessibility features that you can't do just by having a &lt;code&gt;paint()&lt;/code&gt; method print a pretty picture.  It may not be done the best way however, but it may be a good starting point for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit 8/6 - If it wasn't apparent from the images, each Die is a button you can click. This will move it to the &lt;code&gt;DiceContainer&lt;/code&gt; below.  Looking at the source code you can see that each Die button is drawn dynamically, based on its value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/pgyQp.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/jkYRd.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.stack.imgur.com/9BI34.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt text&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here are the basic steps:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Create a class that extends &lt;code&gt;JComponent&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Call parent constructor &lt;code&gt;super()&lt;/code&gt; in your constructors&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Make sure you class implements &lt;code&gt;MouseListener&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Put this in the constructor:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;enableInputMethods(true);   &#xA;addMouseListener(this);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Override these methods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public Dimension getPreferredSize()  &#xA;public Dimension getMinimumSize()  &#xA;public Dimension getMaximumSize()&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Override this method:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public void paintComponent(Graphics g)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The amount of space you have to work with when drawing your button is defined by &lt;code&gt;getPreferredSize()&lt;/code&gt;, assuming &lt;code&gt;getMinimumSize()&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;getMaximumSize()&lt;/code&gt; return the same value.  I haven't experimented too much with this but, depending on the layout you use for your GUI your button could look completely different.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And finally, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/kdeloach/labs/blob/master/java/yahtzee/src/Dice.java&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;source code&lt;/a&gt;.  In case I missed anything.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastEditorUserId="1672920" LastEditorDisplayName="kevin d" LastEditDate="2016-10-27T07:19:59.620" LastActivityDate="2016-10-27T07:19:59.620" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="2823" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-05T20:49:13.017" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;Regarding Java 1.5 and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Autoboxing#Autoboxing&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;autoboxing&lt;/a&gt; there is an important &quot;quirk&quot; that comes to play when comparing Integer objects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Java, Integer objects with the values -128 to 127 are immutable (that is, for one particular integer value, say 23, all Integer objects instantiated through your program with the value 23 points to the &lt;em&gt;exact&lt;/em&gt; same object).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Example, this returns true:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer i1 = new Integer(127);&#xA;Integer i2 = new Integer(127);&#xA;System.out.println(i1 == i2); //  true&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this returns false:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer i1 = new Integer(128);&#xA;Integer i2 = new Integer(128);&#xA;System.out.println(i1 == i2); //  false&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The == compares by reference (does the variables point to the same object).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This result may or may not differ depending on what JVM you are using. The specification autoboxing for Java 1.5 requires that integers (-128 to 127) always box to the same wrapper object. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A solution? =) One should always use the Integer.equals() method when comparing Integer objects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;System.out.println(i1.equals(i2)); //  true&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More info at &lt;a href=&quot;http://today.java.net/pub/a/today/2005/03/24/autoboxing.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;java.net&lt;/a&gt; Example at &lt;a href=&quot;http://bexhuff.com/2006/11/java-1-5-autoboxing-wackyness&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;bexhuff.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="446" LastEditorUserId="446" LastEditorDisplayName="Andreas H.R. Nilsson" LastEditDate="2008-08-05T20:54:33.337" LastActivityDate="2008-08-05T20:54:33.337" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="2931" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-05T22:23:16.183" Score="16" ViewCount="1132" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have been working with &lt;em&gt;JXTA&lt;/em&gt; 2.3 for the last year or so for a peer-to-peer computing platform I am developing. I am migrating to &lt;em&gt;JXTA&lt;/em&gt; 2.5 and in the process I am trying to clean up a lot of my use of &lt;em&gt;JXTA&lt;/em&gt;. For the most part, I approached &lt;em&gt;JXTA&lt;/em&gt; with a &lt;strong&gt;just make it work&lt;/strong&gt; attitude. I used it to jumpstart creating and managing my peer-to-peer overlay network and providing basic communication services. I would like to use it in a more &lt;em&gt;JXTA&lt;/em&gt; way since I am making changes to move to 2.5 anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My first step would be a basic creation of a custom &lt;code&gt;PeerGroup&lt;/code&gt;. I see some new new mechanisms that are using the &lt;code&gt;META-INF.services&lt;/code&gt; infrastructure of Java. Should I be listing a related &lt;code&gt;PeerGroup&lt;/code&gt; implementing object here with a &lt;em&gt;GUID&lt;/em&gt; in &lt;code&gt;net.jxta.platform.Module&lt;/code&gt;? As I understand it, if I do this, when a group with a spec ID matching the &lt;em&gt;GUID&lt;/em&gt; is encountered and joined or created it should automatically use the matching object. I should be able to just manually tie a &lt;code&gt;PeerGroup&lt;/code&gt; object to the group but this new method using &lt;code&gt;META-INF&lt;/code&gt; seems to be a lot easier to manage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have any pointers or examples of using this infrastructure for &lt;code&gt;PeerGroup&lt;/code&gt; implementation? Also, some general information on the &lt;code&gt;META-INF.services&lt;/code&gt; mechanism in Java would be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="360" LastEditorUserId="2553431" LastEditDate="2015-10-27T09:35:19.443" LastActivityDate="2015-10-27T09:35:19.443" Title="Getting started with a custom JXTA PeerGroup" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;p2p&gt;&lt;jxta&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="2968" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="2985" CreationDate="2008-08-05T23:49:53.560" Score="31" ViewCount="51774" Body="&lt;p&gt;For parsing player commands, I've most often used the &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/lang/String.html#split%28java.lang.String%29&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;split&lt;/a&gt; method to split a string by delimiters and then to then just figure out the rest by a series of &lt;code&gt;if&lt;/code&gt;s or &lt;code&gt;switch&lt;/code&gt;es. What are some different ways of parsing strings in Java?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="362" LastEditorUserId="362" LastEditorDisplayName="Lane" LastEditDate="2014-05-13T17:34:45.040" LastActivityDate="2015-10-27T10:00:40.993" Title="What are the different methods to parse strings in Java?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;string&gt;&lt;parsing&gt;" AnswerCount="15" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="4" ClosedDate="2014-05-13T17:04:48.707" />
<row Id="2969" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-05T23:54:05.533" Score="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;I really like regular expressions. As long as the command strings are fairly simple, you can write a few regexes that could take a few pages of code to manually parse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would suggest you check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.regular-expressions.info&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.regular-expressions.info&lt;/a&gt; for a good intro to regexes, as well as specific examples for Java.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="124" LastEditorUserId="1035257" LastEditDate="2012-04-03T05:18:33.757" LastActivityDate="2012-04-03T05:18:33.757" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="2971" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-05T23:57:02.577" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;A simple string tokenizer on spaces should work, but there are really many ways you could do this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here is an example using a tokenizer:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String command = &quot;kick person&quot;;&#xA;StringTokenizer tokens = new StringTokenizer(command);&#xA;String action = null;&#xA;&#xA;if (tokens.hasMoreTokens()) {&#xA;    action = tokens.nextToken();&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;if (action != null) {&#xA;    doCommand(action, tokens);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then tokens can be further used for the arguments.  This all assumes no spaces are used in the arguments... so you might want to roll your own simple parsing mechanism (like getting the first whitespace and using text before as the action, or using a regular expression if you don't mind the speed hit), just abstract it out so it can be used anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-08-05T23:57:02.577" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="2977" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-06T00:16:25.020" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;I would look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.com/search?q=Zork+in+Java&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Java migrations&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zork&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Zork&lt;/a&gt;, and lean towards a simple &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Natural_language_processing&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Natural Language Processor&lt;/a&gt; (driven either by tokenizing or regex) such as the following (from this link):&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&#xA;    public static boolean simpleNLP( String inputline, String keywords[])&#xA;    {&#xA;        int i;&#xA;        int maxToken = keywords.length;&#xA;        int to,from;&#xA;        if( inputline.length() = inputline.length()) return false; // check for blank and empty lines&#xA;        while( to &gt;=0 )&#xA;        {&#xA;            to = inputline.indexOf(' ',from);&#xA;            if( to &gt; 0){&#xA;                lexed.addElement(inputline.substring(from,to));&#xA;                from = to;&#xA;                while( inputline.charAt(from) == ' '&#xA;                &amp;&amp; from = keywords.length) { status = true; break;}&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;        return status;&#xA;    }&#xA;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anything which gives a programmer a reason to look at Zork again is good in my book, just watch out for Grues.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="user2189331" LastEditorUserId="92" LastEditorDisplayName="Justin Standard" LastEditDate="2008-08-06T16:20:17.193" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T16:20:17.193" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="2985" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-06T00:42:00.817" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;I assume you're trying to make the command interface as forgiving as possible. If this is the case, I suggest you use an algorithm similar to this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Read in the string&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Split the string into tokens&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use a dictionary to convert synonyms to a common form &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For example, convert &quot;hit&quot;, &quot;punch&quot;, &quot;strike&quot;, and &quot;kick&quot; all to &quot;hit&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Perform actions on an unordered, inclusive base&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unordered&lt;/strong&gt; - &quot;punch the monkey in the face&quot; is the same thing as &quot;the face in the monkey punch&quot;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inclusive&lt;/strong&gt; - If the command is supposed to be &quot;punch the monkey in the face&quot; and they supply &quot;punch monkey&quot;, you should check how many commands this matches. If only one command, do this action. It might even be a good idea to have command priorities, and even if there were even matches, it would perform the top action.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="432" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T00:42:00.817" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3049" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="3054" CreationDate="2008-08-06T03:19:19.470" Score="29" ViewCount="9785" Body="&lt;p&gt;I need to send and receive data over serial connections (RS-232 and RS-422).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do I set up and communicate with such a connection?  How do I figure out what the configuration settings (e.g. baud rate) should be and how do I set them?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In particular I am looking to do this in Java, C/C++, or one of the major Unix shells but I also have some interest in serial programming using Windows/Hyperterminal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="462" LastActivityDate="2016-01-28T18:00:18.230" Title="How do I configure and communicate with a serial port?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;c++&gt;&lt;windows&gt;&lt;unix&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="5" />
<row Id="3054" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3049" CreationDate="2008-08-06T03:27:43.323" Score="23" Body="&lt;p&gt;Build a time machine and go back to 1987? Ho ho.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, no more snarky comments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;How do I figure out what the configuration settings (e.g. baud rate) should be...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read the datasheet? Ok, ok. Seriously, last one. If you don't know the baud rate of the device you are trying to communicate with, you have two choices. Start guessing, or possibly bust out an o-scope. If you need a good starting point, let me suggest 9600-8-N-1. My suspicion is you can get there with brute force relatively quickly. There's a third option of having an old-school ninja who can tell just by the LOOK of the garbled characters at some standard baud rate what actual baud rate is. An impressive party trick to be sure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hopefully though you have access to this information. In unix/linux, you can get ahold of minicom to play with the serial port directly. This should make it fairly quick to get the configuration figured out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;one of the major Unix shells&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Unix the serial port(s) is/are file-mapped into the /dev/ subdir. ttyS0, for example. If you setup the correct baud rate and whatnot using minicom, you can even cat stuff to that file to send stuff out there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On to the meat of the question, you can access it programmatically through the POSIX headers. termios.h is the big one. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;See: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.easysw.com/~mike/serial/serial.html#3_1&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.easysw.com/~mike/serial/serial.html#3_1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strike&gt;&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;(NOT AVAILABLE ANYMORE)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;but I also have some interest in serial programming using Windows/Hyperterminal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hyperterminal and minicom are basically the same program. As for how Windows let's you get access to the serial port, I'll leave that question for someone else. I haven't done that in Windows since the Win95 days.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="2089740" LastEditorUserId="982161" LastEditorDisplayName="lbrandy" LastEditDate="2016-01-28T17:59:11.807" LastActivityDate="2016-01-28T17:59:11.807" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3060" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3049" CreationDate="2008-08-06T03:35:50.093" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;From the other side, if you want to do it using C#, which will run on both Windows and Linux--with some &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mono-project.com/HowToSystemIOPorts&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;limitations&lt;/a&gt; (EDIT: which may be out of date. I have no way to test it.). Just create a &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/system.io.ports.serialport.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;SerialPort&lt;/a&gt; object, set its baudrate, port and any other odd settings, call open on it, and write out your byte[]s. After all the setup, the SerialPort object acts very similar to any networked stream, so it should be easy enough to figure out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And as ibrandy states, you need to know all these settings, like baud rate, before you even start attempting to communicate to any serial device. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="429" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T03:35:50.093" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3090" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3049" CreationDate="2008-08-06T05:04:57.353" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;At work we use teraterm and realterm for checking serial data is correctly formatted. Also we have a hardware splitter with a switch so we can monitor traffic to our application via a cable back to another port.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Windows allows you access to the serial port via CreateFile. That gives you a handle and from there you can configure access.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="342" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T05:04:57.353" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3285" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-06T11:08:52.283" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;In Java there are two basic types in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/Concepts.doc.html#22930&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JVM&lt;/a&gt;. 1) Primitive types and 2) Reference Types. int is a primitive type and Integer is a class type (which is kind of reference type).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Primitive values do not share state with other primitive values. A variable whose type is a primitive type always holds a primitive value of that type.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int aNumber = 4;&#xA;int anotherNum = aNumber;&#xA;aNumber += 6;&#xA;System.out.println(anotherNum); // Prints 4&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;An object is a dynamically created class instance or an array. The reference values (often just references) are pointers to these objects and a special null reference, which refers to no object. There may be many references to the same object.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer aNumber = Integer.valueOf(4);&#xA;Integer anotherNumber = aNumber; // anotherNumber references the &#xA;                                 // same object as aNumber&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also in Java everything is passed by value. With objects the value that is passed is the reference to the object. So another difference between int and Integer in java is how they are passed in method calls. For example in&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public int add(int a, int b) {&#xA;    return a + b;&#xA;}&#xA;final int two = 2;&#xA;int sum = add(1, two);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The variable &lt;em&gt;two&lt;/em&gt; is passed as the primitive integer type 2. Whereas in&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public int add(Integer a, Integer b) {&#xA;    return a.intValue() + b.intValue();&#xA;}&#xA;final Integer two = Integer.valueOf(2);&#xA;int sum = add(Integer.valueOf(1), two);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The variable &lt;em&gt;two&lt;/em&gt; is passed as a reference to an object that holds the integer value 2.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;@WolfmanDragon:&#xA;Pass by reference would work like so:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public void increment(int x) {&#xA;  x = x + 1;&#xA;}&#xA;int a = 1;&#xA;increment(a);&#xA;// a is now 2&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When increment is called it passes a reference (pointer) to variable &lt;em&gt;a&lt;/em&gt;. And the &lt;em&gt;increment&lt;/em&gt; function directly modifies variable &lt;em&gt;a&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And for object types it would work as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public void increment(Integer x) {&#xA;  x = Integer.valueOf(x.intValue() + 1);&#xA;}&#xA;Integer a = Integer.valueOf(1);&#xA;increment(a);&#xA;// a is now 2&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you see the difference now?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="486" LastEditorUserId="486" LastEditorDisplayName="grom" LastEditDate="2009-02-05T06:58:19.783" LastActivityDate="2009-02-05T06:58:19.783" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="3464" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="564" CreationDate="2008-08-06T14:33:33.090" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;One more thing that I don't see in previous answers:&#xA;In Java the primitive wrappers classes like Integer, Double, Float, Boolean... and String are suposed to be invariant, so that when you pass an instance of those classes the invoked method couldn't alter your data in any way, in opositin with most of other classes, which internal data could be altered by its public methods. So that this classes only has 'getter' methods, no 'setters', besides the constructor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In a java program String literals are stored in a separate portion of heap memory, only a instance for literal, to save memory reusing those instances&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="518" OwnerDisplayName="Telcontar" LastEditorUserId="42439" LastEditDate="2010-03-05T02:48:56.727" LastActivityDate="2010-03-05T02:48:56.727" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3485" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="126" CreationDate="2008-08-06T14:43:54.830" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;i can be wrong because i'm autodidact, but i NEVER user public properties in my Java clases, they are allways private or protected, so that outside code must access by getters/setters. it's better for mainteance / modification purposes. And for inside class code... if getter method is trivial i use the property directly, but i allways use the setter methods because i could easily add code to fire events if i wish&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="518" OwnerDisplayName="Telcontar" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T14:43:54.830" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3539" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-06T15:18:18.957" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;@CodingTheWheel Heres your code, a bit clean up and through eclipse (&lt;kbd&gt;ctrl&lt;/kbd&gt;+&lt;kbd&gt;shift&lt;/kbd&gt;+&lt;kbd&gt;f&lt;/kbd&gt;) and the inserted back here :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Including the four spaces in front each line.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static boolean simpleNLP(String inputline, String keywords[]) {&#xA;    if (inputline.length() &amp;lt; 1)&#xA;        return false;&#xA;&#xA;    List&amp;lt;String&amp;gt; lexed = new ArrayList&amp;lt;String&amp;gt;(); &#xA;    for (String ele : inputline.split(&quot; &quot;)) {&#xA;        lexed.add(ele);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    boolean status = false;&#xA;    to = 0;&#xA;    for (i = 0; i &amp;lt; lexed.size(); i++) {&#xA;        String s = (String) lexed.get(i);&#xA;        if (s.equalsIgnoreCase(keywords[to])) {&#xA;            to++;&#xA;            if (to &amp;gt;= keywords.length) {&#xA;                status = true;&#xA;                break;&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;    }&#xA;    return status;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="86" LastEditorUserId="7226" LastEditorDisplayName="svrist" LastEditDate="2015-08-20T22:13:23.197" LastActivityDate="2015-08-20T22:13:23.197" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3565" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-06T15:40:46.917" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;When the separator String for the command is allways the same String or char (like the &quot;;&quot;) y recomend you use the StrinkTokenizer class:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/util/StringTokenizer.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;StringTokenizer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but when the separator varies or is complex y recomend you to use the regular expresions, wich can be used by the String class itself, method split, since 1.4. It uses the Pattern class from the java.util.regex package&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/util/regex/Pattern.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Pattern&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="518" OwnerDisplayName="Telcontar" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T15:40:46.917" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3616" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2968" CreationDate="2008-08-06T16:14:45.460" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;Sun itself recommends staying away from StringTokenizer and using the String.spilt method instead. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You'll also want to look at the Pattern class.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="543" LastActivityDate="2008-08-06T16:14:45.460" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="3881" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="3886" CreationDate="2008-08-06T19:26:30.627" Score="373" ViewCount="104890" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a simple setter method for a property and &lt;code&gt;null&lt;/code&gt; is not appropriate for this particular property. I have always been torn in this situation: should I throw an &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/lang/IllegalArgumentException.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;IllegalArgumentException&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or a &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/lang/NullPointerException.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;NullPointerException&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;? From the javadocs, both seem appropriate. Is there some kind of an understood standard?  Or is this just one of those things that you should do whatever you prefer and both are really correct?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastEditorUserId="3156863" LastEditorDisplayName="Chris Fournier" LastEditDate="2014-01-17T12:18:34.950" LastActivityDate="2016-09-23T10:07:12.967" Title="IllegalArgumentException or NullPointerException for a null parameter?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;exception&gt;&lt;null&gt;&lt;nullpointerexception&gt;&lt;illegalargumentexception&gt;" AnswerCount="27" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="101" ClosedDate="2016-09-23T13:34:31.323" />
<row Id="3886" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-06T19:29:24.427" Score="201" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not a Java developer, but just from the sound of it, it seems like an &lt;code&gt;IllegalArgumentException&lt;/code&gt; is called for if you don't want null to be an allowed value, and the &lt;code&gt;NullPointerException&lt;/code&gt; would be thrown if you were trying to &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; a variable that turns out to be null.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="35" LastEditorUserId="1479414" LastEditDate="2013-03-01T14:43:30.843" LastActivityDate="2013-03-01T14:43:30.843" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="3890" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-06T19:31:11.070" Score="11" Body="&lt;p&gt;If it's a &lt;code&gt;setter&lt;/code&gt; method and &lt;code&gt;null&lt;/code&gt; is being passed to it, I think it would make more sense to throw an &lt;code&gt;IllegalArgumentException&lt;/code&gt;. A &lt;code&gt;NullPointerException&lt;/code&gt; seems to make more sense in the case where you're attempting to actually use the &lt;code&gt;null&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, if you're using it and it's &lt;code&gt;null&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;NullPointer&lt;/code&gt;. If it's being passed in and it's &lt;code&gt;null&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;IllegalArgument&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="560" LastEditorUserId="2014130" LastEditDate="2016-08-30T10:11:03.347" LastActivityDate="2016-08-30T10:11:03.347" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4080" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="79845" CreationDate="2008-08-06T22:45:27.543" Score="93" ViewCount="32544" Body="&lt;p&gt;What code analysis tools do you use on your Java projects?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am interested in all kinds&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;static code analysis tools (FindBugs, PMD, and any others)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;code coverage tools (Cobertura, Emma, and any others)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;any other instrumentation-based tools &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;anything else, if I'm missing something&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If applicable, also state what build tools you use and how well these tools integrate with both your IDEs and build tools. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a tool is only available a specific way (as an IDE plugin, or, say, a build tool plugin) that information is also worth noting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="235" LastEditorUserId="1288" LastEditorDisplayName="Ned Batchelder" LastEditDate="2012-08-09T03:29:08.923" LastActivityDate="2014-04-29T06:05:47.530" Title="What code analysis tools do you use for your Java projects?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;code-coverage&gt;&lt;static-analysis&gt;" AnswerCount="12" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="55" ClosedDate="2012-05-05T13:39:59.117" />
<row Id="4149" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="154588" CreationDate="2008-08-06T23:57:10.173" Score="64" ViewCount="27978" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have an application that writes information to file. This information is used post-execution to determine pass/failure/correctness of the application. I'd like to be able to read the file as it is being written so that I can do these pass/failure/correctness checks in realtime.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I assume it is possible to do this, but what are the gotchas involved when using Java? If the reading catches up to the writing, will it just wait for more writes up until the file is closed, or will the read throw an exception at this point? If the latter, what do I do then? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My intuition is currently pushing me towards BufferedStreams. Is this the way to go?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="488" LastEditorUserId="845306" LastEditDate="2011-12-22T23:09:42.943" LastActivityDate="2016-11-15T13:48:09.113" Title="How do I use Java to read from a file that is actively being written?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;file&gt;&lt;file-io&gt;" AnswerCount="10" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="21" />
<row Id="4166" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4080" CreationDate="2008-08-07T00:20:41.750" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;We use FindBugs and JDepend integrated with Ant. We use JUnit but we're not using any coverage tool. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm not using it integrated to Rational Application Developer (the IDE I'm using to develop J2EE applications) because I like how neat it looks when you run javac in the Windows console. :P&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="527" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T00:20:41.750" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4188" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4149" CreationDate="2008-08-07T00:31:47.203" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Not Java per-se, but you may run into issues where you have written something to a file, but it hasn't been actually written yet - it might be in a cache somewhere, and reading from the same file may not actually give you the new information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Short version - use flush() or whatever the relevant system call is to ensure that your data is actually written to the file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note I am not talking about the OS level disk cache - if your data gets into here, it should appear in a read() after this point.  It may be that the language itself caches writes, waiting until a buffer fills up or file is flushed/closed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="188" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T00:31:47.203" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4206" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4149" CreationDate="2008-08-07T00:37:44.880" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've never tried it, but you should write a test case to see if reading from a stream after you have hit the end will work, regardless of if there is more data written to the file.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there a reason you can't use a piped input/output stream?  Is the data being written and read from the same application (if so, you have the data, why do you need to read from the file)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, maybe read till end of file, then monitor for changes and seek to where you left off and continue... though watch out for race conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T00:37:44.880" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4242" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="4247" CreationDate="2008-08-07T01:05:15.420" Score="39" ViewCount="5503" Body="&lt;p&gt;I want to convert a primitive to a string, and I tried:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;myInt.toString();&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This fails with the error:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;int cannot be dereferenced&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, I get that primitives are not reference types (ie, not an Object) and so cannot have methods.  However, Java 5 introduced autoboxing and unboxing (a la C#... which I never liked in C#, but that's beside the point).  So with autoboxing, I would expect the above to convert myInt to an Integer and then call toString() on that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, I believe C# allows such a call, unless I remember incorrectly.  Is this just an unfortunate shortcoming of Java's autoboxing/unboxing specification, or is there a good reason for this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastEditorUserId="131433" LastEditorDisplayName="erickson" LastEditDate="2012-05-23T14:28:15.333" LastActivityDate="2014-01-30T23:26:36.633" Title="Why doesn't Java autoboxing extend to method invocations of methods of the autoboxed types?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;autoboxing&gt;" AnswerCount="8" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="4" />
<row Id="4247" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4242" CreationDate="2008-08-07T01:09:17.547" Score="41" Body="&lt;p&gt;Java autoboxing/unboxing doesn't go to the extent to allow you to dereference a primitive, so your compiler prevents it. Your compiler still knows &lt;code&gt;myInt&lt;/code&gt; as a primitive.  There's a paper about this issue at &lt;a href=&quot;http://jcp.org/aboutJava/communityprocess/jsr/tiger/autoboxing.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;jcp.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Autoboxing is mainly useful during assignment or parameter passing -- allowing you to pass a primitive as an object (or vice versa), or assign a primitive to an object (or vice versa).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So unfortunately, you would have to do it like this: (kudos Patrick, I switched to your way)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer.toString(myInt);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="92" LastEditorUserId="866022" LastEditorDisplayName="Justin Standard" LastEditDate="2012-05-23T14:14:20.383" LastActivityDate="2012-05-23T14:14:20.383" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4256" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4242" CreationDate="2008-08-07T01:16:21.263" Score="24" Body="&lt;p&gt;Ditto on what Justin said, but you should do this instead:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Integer.toString(myInt);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It saves an allocation or two and is more readable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="429" LastEditorUserId="429" LastEditorDisplayName="Patrick" LastEditDate="2008-08-13T01:43:32.960" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T01:43:32.960" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4384" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4242" CreationDate="2008-08-07T04:16:20.480" Score="6" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;seems like a shortcoming of the&#xA;  specification to me&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are more shortcomings and this is a subtle topic. Check &lt;a href=&quot;http://kiranthakkar.blogspot.com/2007/05/method-overloading-with-new-features-of.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; out:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class methodOverloading{&#xA;   public static void hello(Integer x){&#xA;      System.out.println(&quot;Integer&quot;);&#xA;   }&#xA;&#xA;   public static void hello(long x){&#xA;      System.out.println(&quot;long&quot;);&#xA;   }&#xA;&#xA;   public static void main(String[] args){&#xA;      int i = 5;&#xA;      hello(i);&#xA;   }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here &quot;long&quot; would be printed (haven't checked it myself), because the compiler choses widening over autoboxing. Be careful when using autoboxing or don't use it at all!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastEditorUserId="122" LastEditorDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditDate="2008-08-07T07:26:31.047" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T07:26:31.047" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4492" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4080" CreationDate="2008-08-07T07:18:26.710" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://checkstyle.sourceforge.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Checkstyle&lt;/a&gt; is another one I've used at a previous company... it's mainly for style checking, but it can do some static analysis too.  Also, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.atlassian.com/software/clover/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Clover&lt;/a&gt; for code coverage, though be aware it is not a free tool.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T07:18:26.710" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4493" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4080" CreationDate="2008-08-07T07:21:49.230" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;We are using FindBugs and Checkstyle as well as Clover for Code Coverage. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think it's important to have some kind of static analysis, supporting your development. Unfortunately it's still not widely spread that these tools are important.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T07:21:49.230" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4498" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4149" CreationDate="2008-08-07T07:25:02.580" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;The answer seems to be &quot;no&quot; ... and &quot;yes&quot;. There seems to be no real way to know if a file is open for writing by another application. So, reading from such a file will just progress until content is exhausted. I took Mike's advice and wrote some test code:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Writer.java writes a string to file and then waits for the user to hit enter before writing another line to file. The idea being that it could be started up, then a reader can be started to see how it copes with the &quot;partial&quot; file. The reader I wrote is in Reader.java.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Writer.java&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class Writer extends Object&#xA;{&#xA;    Writer () {&#xA;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public static String[] strings = &#xA;        {&#xA;            &quot;Hello World&quot;, &#xA;            &quot;Goodbye World&quot;&#xA;        };&#xA;&#xA;    public static void main(String[] args) &#xA;        throws java.io.IOException {&#xA;&#xA;        java.io.PrintWriter pw =&#xA;            new java.io.PrintWriter(new java.io.FileOutputStream(&quot;out.txt&quot;), true);&#xA;&#xA;        for(String s : strings) {&#xA;            pw.println(s);&#xA;            System.in.read();&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        pw.close();&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reader.java&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class Reader extends Object&#xA;{&#xA;    Reader () {&#xA;&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public static void main(String[] args) &#xA;        throws Exception {&#xA;&#xA;        java.io.FileInputStream in = new java.io.FileInputStream(&quot;out.txt&quot;);&#xA;&#xA;        java.nio.channels.FileChannel fc = in.getChannel();&#xA;        java.nio.ByteBuffer bb = java.nio.ByteBuffer.allocate(10);&#xA;&#xA;        while(fc.read(bb) &amp;gt;= 0) {&#xA;            bb.flip();&#xA;            while(bb.hasRemaining()) {&#xA;                System.out.println((char)bb.get());&#xA;            }&#xA;            bb.clear();&#xA;        }&#xA;&#xA;        System.exit(0);&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;No guarantees that this code is best practice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This leaves the option suggested by Mike of periodically checking if there is new data to be read from the file. This then requires user intervention to close the file reader when it is determined that the reading is completed. Or, the reader needs to be made aware the content of the file and be able to determine and end of write condition. If the content were XML, the end of document could be used to signal this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="488" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T07:25:02.580" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4630" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="478658" CreationDate="2008-08-07T12:26:50.707" Score="8" ViewCount="2200" Body="&lt;p&gt;Example: I have two shared objects (same should apply to .dlls). The first shared object is from a third-party library, we'll call it libA.so. I have wrapped some of this with JNI and created my own library, libB.so. Now libB depends on libA.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When webstarting, both libraries are places in some webstart working area. My java code attempts to load libB. At this point the system loader will attempt to load libA which is not in the system library path (java.library.path won't help this). The end result is that libB has an unsatisfied link and cannot be used. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have tried loading libA before libB, but that still does not work. Seems the OS wants to do that loading for me. Is there any way I can make this work other than statically  compiling?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="287" LastActivityDate="2011-11-07T17:35:00.647" Title="How can I Java webstart multiple, dependent, native libraries?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;jni&gt;&lt;java-web-start&gt;&lt;nativelibrary&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="4922" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5091" CreationDate="2008-08-07T16:30:32.180" Score="21" ViewCount="3650" Body="&lt;p&gt;I saw this in &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/a/4384/697449&quot;&gt;an answer to another question&lt;/a&gt;, in reference to shortcomings of the java spec:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;There are more shortcomings and this is a subtle topic. Check &lt;a href=&quot;http://kiranthakkar.blogspot.com/2007/05/method-overloading-with-new-features-of.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; out:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class methodOverloading{&#xA;     public static void hello(Integer x){&#xA;          System.out.println(&quot;Integer&quot;);&#xA;     }&#xA;&#xA;     public static void hello(long x){&#xA;          System.out.println(&quot;long&quot;);&#xA;     }&#xA;&#xA;     public static void main(String[] args){&#xA;         int i = 5;&#xA;         hello(i);&#xA;     }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Here &quot;long&quot; would be printed (haven't checked it myself), because the compiler choses &gt;widening over autoboxing. Be careful when using autoboxing or don't use it at all!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Are we sure that this is actually an example of widening instead of autoboxing, or is it something else entirely?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On my initial scanning, I would agree with the statement that the output would be &quot;long&quot; on the basis of &lt;code&gt;i&lt;/code&gt; being declared as a primitive and not an object.  However, if you changed &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;hello(long x)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;to&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;hello(Long x)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the output would print &quot;Integer&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What's really going on here?  I know nothing about the compilers/bytecode interpreters for java...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="670" LastEditorUserId="697449" LastEditorDisplayName="Andy" LastEditDate="2012-03-11T22:06:40.360" LastActivityDate="2012-03-11T22:06:40.360" Title="Is this really widening vs autoboxing?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;primitive&gt;&lt;autoboxing&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="4932" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4922" CreationDate="2008-08-07T16:36:25.447" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Yes it is, try it out in a test.  You will see &quot;long&quot; printed.  It is widening because Java will choose to widen the int into a long before it chooses to autobox it to an Integer, so the hello(long) method is chosen to be called.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4242/why-cant-i-call-tostring-on-a-java-primitive#4384&quot;&gt;the original post being referenced&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Further Edit: The reason the second option would print Integer is because there is no &quot;widening&quot; into a larger primitive as an option, so it MUST box it up, thus Integer is the only option.  Furthermore, java will only autobox to the original type, so it would give a compiler error if you leave the hello(Long) and removed hello(Integer).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastEditorUserId="122" LastEditorDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditDate="2008-08-07T16:41:42.020" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T16:41:42.020" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5042" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4630" CreationDate="2008-08-07T17:53:38.113" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure if this would be handled exactly the same way for webstart, but we ran into this situation in a desktop application when dealing with a set of native libraries (dlls in our case).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Loading libA before libB should work, unless one of those libraries has a dependency that is unaccounted for and not in the path. My understanding is that once it gets to a system loadLibrary call (i.e. Java has found the library in its java.library.path and is now telling the OS to load it) - it is completely dependent on the operating system to find any dependent libraries, because at that point it is the operating system that is loading the library for the process, and the OS only knows how to look in the system path. That seems hard to set in the case of a Webstart app, but there is a way around this that does not involve static compiling. You may be able to shuffle where your libraries are - I am unsure &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you use a custom classloader, you can override loadLibrary and findLibrary so that it can locate your libraries from within a jar in your classpath, and if you also make it aware of your native library dependencies (i.e. libB depends on libA depends on libX, then when loading libB you can catch yourself and ensure you load libA first, and in checking that notice and load libX first. Then the OS doesn't try to find a library that isn't in your path. It's klunky and a bit painful, but ensuring Java finds them and loads them all in the correct order can work.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="235" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T17:53:38.113" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5091" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4922" CreationDate="2008-08-07T18:18:34.897" Score="12" Body="&lt;p&gt;In the first case, you have a widening conversion happening. This can be see when runinng the &quot;javap&quot; utility program (included w/ the JDK), on the compiled class:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void main(java.lang.String[]);&#xA;  Code:&#xA;   0:   iconst_ 5&#xA;   1:   istore_ 1&#xA;   2:   iload_ 1&#xA;   3:   i2l&#xA;   4:   invokestatic    #6; //Method hello:(J)V&#xA;   7:   return&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Clearly, you see the I2L, which is the mnemonic for the widening Integer-To-Long bytecode instruction. See reference &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/docs/books/jvms/second_edition/html/Instructions2.doc6.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And in the other case, replacing the &quot;long x&quot; with the object &quot;Long x&quot; signature, you'll have this code in the main method:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void main(java.lang.String[]);&#xA;  Code:&#xA;   0:   iconst_ 5&#xA;   1:   istore_ 1&#xA;   2:   iload_ 1&#xA;   3:   invokestatic    #6; //Method java/lang/Integer.valueOf:(I)Ljava/lang/Integer;&#xA;   6:   invokestatic    #7; //Method hello:(Ljava/lang/Integer;)V&#xA;   9:   return&#xA;&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you see the compiler has created the instruction Integer.valueOf(int), to box the primitive inside the wrapper.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="861" OwnerDisplayName="camilojd" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T18:18:34.897" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5164" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4922" CreationDate="2008-08-07T19:02:29.630" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Another interesting thing with this example is the method overloading. The combination of type widening and method overloading only working because the compiler has to make a decision of which method to choose. Consider the following example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public static void hello(Collection x){&#xA;   System.out.println(&quot;Collection&quot;);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public static void hello(List x){&#xA;   System.out.println(&quot;List&quot;);&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;public static void main(String[] args){&#xA;   Collection col = new ArrayList();&#xA;   hello(col);&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It doesn't use the run-time type which is List, it uses the compile-time type which is Collection and thus prints &quot;Collection&quot;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I encourage your to read &lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=ZZOiqZQIbRMC&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Effective Java&lt;/a&gt;, which opened my eyes to some corner cases of the JLS.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T19:02:29.630" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5222" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5224" CreationDate="2008-08-07T19:39:31.240" Score="33" ViewCount="74637" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the Java equivalent of PHP's &lt;code&gt;$_POST&lt;/code&gt;? After searching the web for an hour, I'm still nowhere closer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="429" LastEditorUserId="507738" LastEditorDisplayName="Stu Thompson" LastEditDate="2015-07-25T13:10:57.280" LastActivityDate="2016-11-24T11:12:07.787" Title="Accessing post variables using Java Servlets" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;http&gt;&lt;servlets&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="7" />
<row Id="5224" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5222" CreationDate="2008-08-07T19:43:36.113" Score="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;Your &lt;code&gt;HttpServletRequest&lt;/code&gt; object has a &lt;code&gt;getParameter(String paramName)&lt;/code&gt; method that can be used to get parameter values.  &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javaee/5/docs/api/javax/servlet/ServletRequest.html#getParameter(java.lang.String)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://java.sun.com/javaee/5/docs/api/javax/servlet/ServletRequest.html#getParameter(java.lang.String)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="75" LastEditorDisplayName="Ryan Ahearn" LastEditDate="2011-06-21T17:54:52.550" LastActivityDate="2011-06-21T17:54:52.550" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5227" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5222" CreationDate="2008-08-07T19:47:30.490" Score="17" Body="&lt;p&gt;POST variables should be accessible via the request object: &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/products/servlet/2.3/javadoc/javax/servlet/ServletRequest.html#getParameterMap()&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;HttpRequest.getParameterMap()&lt;/a&gt;. The exception is if the form is sending multipart MIME data (the FORM has &lt;strong&gt;enctype=&quot;multipart/form-data&quot;&lt;/strong&gt;). In that case, you need to parse the byte stream with a MIME parser. You can write your own or use an existing one like the Apache &lt;a href=&quot;http://commons.apache.org/fileupload/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Commons File Upload&lt;/a&gt; API.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="304" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T19:47:30.490" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5328" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5351" CreationDate="2008-08-07T21:17:56.813" Score="28" ViewCount="4741" Body="&lt;p&gt;So, in Java, the first line of your constructor HAS to be a call to super... be it implicitly calling super(), or explicitly calling another constructor.  What I want to know is, why can't I put a try block around that?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My specific case is that I have a mock class for a test.  There is no default constructor, but I want one to make the tests simpler to read.  I also want to wrap the exceptions thrown from the constructor into a RuntimeException.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, what I want to do is effectively this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class MyClassMock extends MyClass {&#xA;    public MyClassMock() {&#xA;        try {&#xA;            super(0);&#xA;        } catch (Exception e) {&#xA;            throw new RuntimeException(e);&#xA;        }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    // Mocked methods&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But Java complains that super isn't the first statement.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My workaround:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public class MyClassMock extends MyClass {&#xA;    public static MyClassMock construct() {&#xA;        try {&#xA;            return new MyClassMock();&#xA;        } catch (Exception e) {&#xA;            throw new RuntimeException(e);&#xA;        }&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    public MyClassMock() throws Exception {&#xA;        super(0);&#xA;    }&#xA;&#xA;    // Mocked methods&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is this the best workaround?  Why doesn't Java let me do the former?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My best guess as to the &quot;why&quot; is that Java doesn't want to let me have a constructed object in a potentially inconsistent state... however, in doing a mock, I don't care about that.  It seems I should be able to do the above... or at least I know that the above is safe for my case... or seems as though it should be anyways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am overriding any methods I use from the tested class, so there is no risk that I am using uninitialized variables.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastEditorUserId="1345224" LastEditDate="2014-11-06T01:45:28.287" LastActivityDate="2014-11-06T03:39:06.700" Title="Why can't I use a try block around my super() call?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;exception&gt;&lt;mocking&gt;&lt;try-catch&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="5351" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5328" CreationDate="2008-08-07T21:32:34.367" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, compilers can't work on theoretical principles, and even though you may know that it is safe in your case, if they allowed it, it would have to be safe for all cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, the compiler isn't stopping just you, it's stopping everyone, including all those that don't know that it is unsafe and needs special handling. There are probably other reasons for this as well, as all languages usually have ways to do &lt;em&gt;unsafe&lt;/em&gt; things if one knows how to deal with them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In C# .NET there are similar provisions, and the only way to declare a constructor that calls a base constructor is this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public ClassName(...) : base(...)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;in doing so, the base constructor will be called before the body of the constructor, and you cannot change this order.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="267" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T21:32:34.367" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5357" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5328" CreationDate="2008-08-07T21:41:59.917" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't know how Java is implemented internally, but if the constructor of the superclass throws an exception, then there isn't a instance of the class you extend.  It would be impossible to call the &lt;code&gt;toString()&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;equals()&lt;/code&gt; methods, for example, since they are inherited in most cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Java may allow a try/catch around the super() call in the constructor if 1. you override ALL methods from the superclasses, and 2. you don't use the super.XXX() clause, but that all sounds too complicated to me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="518" LastEditorUserId="44390" LastEditDate="2011-11-08T19:14:00.590" LastActivityDate="2011-11-08T19:14:00.590" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5360" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5328" CreationDate="2008-08-07T21:43:37.463" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can't presume to have a deep understanding of Java internals, but it is my understanding that, when a compiler needs to instantiate a derived class, it has to first create the base (and its base before that(...)) and then slap on the extensions made in the subclass. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So it is not even the danger of uninited variables or anything like that at all. When you try to do something in the subclass' constructor &lt;em&gt;before&lt;/em&gt; the base class' &lt;strong&gt;constructor&lt;/strong&gt;, you are basically asking the compiler to extend a base object instance that doesn't exist yet.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit:In your case, &lt;strong&gt;MyClass&lt;/strong&gt; becomes the base object, and &lt;strong&gt;MyClassMock&lt;/strong&gt; is a subclass.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="227" LastEditorUserId="227" LastEditorDisplayName="Ishmaeel" LastEditDate="2008-08-07T21:52:45.557" LastActivityDate="2008-08-07T21:52:45.557" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5527" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="5532" CreationDate="2008-08-08T01:04:02.300" Score="18" ViewCount="2907" Body="&lt;p&gt;I just saw a &lt;a href=&quot;http://stackoverflow.com/questions/5516/what-happened-to-all-of-the-java-developers-how-can-i-get-started-in-net#5522&quot;&gt;comment of suggesting J#&lt;/a&gt;, and it made me wonder... is there a real, beneficial use of J# over Java?  So, my feeling is that the only reason you would even consider using J# is that management has decreed that the company should jump on the Java bandwagon... and the .NET bandwagon.  If you use J#, you are effectively losing the biggest benefit of picking Java... rich cross platform support.  Sure there is Mono, but it's not as richly supported or as full featured right?  I remember hearing Forms are not fully (perhaps at all) supported.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm not trying to bash .NET here, I'm just saying, if you are going to go the Microsoft route, why not just use C#?  If you are going to go the Java route, why would J# enter the picture?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm hoping to find some real world cases here, so please especially respond if you've ACTUALLY used J# in a REAL project, and why.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-09-12T20:27:48.340" Title="Is there a real benefit of using J#?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;j#&gt;" AnswerCount="8" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="5532" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5527" CreationDate="2008-08-08T01:11:58.680" Score="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;J# is no longer included in VS2008. Unless you already have J# code, you should probably stay away.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/vjsharp/default.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;j# product page:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Since customers have told us that the&#xA;  existing J# feature set largely meets&#xA;  their needs and usage of J# is&#xA;  declining, Microsoft is retiring the&#xA;  Visual J# product and Java Language&#xA;  Conversion Assistant tool to better&#xA;  allocate resources for other customer&#xA;  requirements. The J# language and JLCA&#xA;  tool will not be available in future&#xA;  versions of Visual Studio. To preserve&#xA;  existing customer investments in J#,&#xA;  Microsoft will continue to support the&#xA;  J# and JLCA technology that shipped&#xA;  with Visual Studio 2005 through to&#xA;  2015 as per our product life-cycle&#xA;  strategy. For more information, see&#xA;  Expanded Microsoft Support Lifecycle&#xA;  Policy for Business &amp;amp; Development&#xA;  Products.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="100" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T01:11:58.680" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5536" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5527" CreationDate="2008-08-08T01:19:01.427" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;The whole purpose of J# is to ease the transition of Java developers to the .NET environment which didn't work so well (I guessing here) so Microsoft dropped J# from Visual Studio 2008.&#xA;For your question, &quot;Is there a real benefit of using J#?&quot;..&#xA;in a nutshell... No..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="463" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T01:19:01.427" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="5538" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5527" CreationDate="2008-08-08T01:21:02.110" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;One of the killers I've found with J# in the past is that there is no built in support for referencing web services. That alone has been enough to deter me from it ever since.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="493" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T01:21:02.110" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5645" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5527" CreationDate="2008-08-08T04:22:32.913" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;C# syntax is so close to Java (and better in some ways) that you might as well learn C# instead of J#.  And since C# is more widely used, you can easily find Java --&gt; C# tutorials on google or check out &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.asp.net/learn&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.asp.net/learn&lt;/a&gt; and watch some videos.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="396" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T04:22:32.913" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="5855" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6687" CreationDate="2008-08-08T12:40:02.793" Score="5" ViewCount="874" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've found many sources that talk about the automated Eclipse PDE process.  I feel these sources don't do a good job explaining what's going on.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can create the deployable package, in a semi-manual process via the Feature Export.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The automated process requires knowledge of how the org.eclipse.pde.build scripts work.  I have gotten a build created, but not for JNLP.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Has anyone ever deployed RCP through JNLP?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Were you able to automate the builds?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="728" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T21:23:23.267" Title="Automate builds for Java RCP for deployment with JNLP" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;build-automation&gt;&lt;rcp&gt;&lt;jnlp&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="6022" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4080" CreationDate="2008-08-08T14:53:12.293" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am looking for many answers to learn about new tools and consolidate this knowledge in a one question/thread, so I doubt there will be 1 true answer to this question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My answer to my own question is that we use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Findbugs to look for common errors bad/coding - run from maven, and also integrates easily into Eclipse&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cobertura for our coverage reports - run from maven&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hudson also has a task-scanner plugin that will display a count of your TODO and FIXMEs, as well as show where they are in the source files.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;All are integrated with Maven 1.x in our case and tied into Hudson, which runs our builds on check-in as well as extra things nightly and weekly. Hudson trend graphs our JUnit tests, coverage, findbugs, as well as open tasks. There is also a Hudson plugin that reports and graphs our compile warnings. We also have several performance tests with their own graphs of performance and memory use over time using the Hudson plots plugin as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="235" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T14:53:12.293" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6222" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7877" CreationDate="2008-08-08T18:17:50.460" Score="8" ViewCount="3869" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is anyone successfully using the latest 64-bit Ganymede release of Eclipse on Windows XP or Vista 64-bit?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Currently I run the normal Eclipse 3.4 distribution on a 32bit JDK and launch &amp;amp; compile my apps with a 64bit JDK. Our previous experience has been that the 64bit Eclipse distro is unstable for us, so I'm curious if anyone is using it successfully.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are using JDK 1.6.0_05.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="235" LastEditorUserId="15352" LastEditorDisplayName="Craig Angus" LastEditDate="2008-10-11T14:41:37.377" LastActivityDate="2015-11-30T00:48:34.950" Title="Eclipse on win64" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;eclipse&gt;&lt;eclipse-3.4&gt;&lt;ganymede&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6352" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3049" CreationDate="2008-08-08T20:24:23.670" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;From Java the &lt;strike&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.rxtx.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;rxtx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strike&gt; (&lt;strong&gt;NOT AVAILABLE ANYMORE&lt;/strong&gt;)library is quite good. It picks up where Sun's serial IO framework left off. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="758" LastEditorUserId="982161" LastEditDate="2016-01-28T18:00:18.230" LastActivityDate="2016-01-28T18:00:18.230" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="6356" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6222" CreationDate="2008-08-08T20:28:49.917" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been successfully using it on Vista x64 for some light Java work.  Nothing too involved and no extra plugins, but basic Java coding has been working without any issues.  I'm using the 3.4M7 build but it looks like the &lt;a href=&quot;http://download.eclipse.org/eclipse/downloads/drops/R-3.4-200806172000/index.php&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;3.4 stable build&lt;/a&gt; supports Vista x64 now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="729" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T20:28:49.917" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6358" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-08T20:35:04.007" Score="52" Body="&lt;p&gt;I tend to follow the design of JDK libraries, especially Collections and Concurrency (Joshua Bloch, Doug Lea, those guys know how to design solid APIs). Anyway, many APIs in the JDK pro-actively throws &lt;code&gt;NullPointerException&lt;/code&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, the Javadoc for &lt;code&gt;Map.containsKey&lt;/code&gt; states:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;@throws NullPointerException if the key is null and this map&#xA;    does not permit null keys (optional).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's perfectly valid to throw your own NPE. The convention is to include the parameter name which was null in the message of the exception. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The pattern goes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;public void someMethod(Object mustNotBeNull) {  &#xA;    if (mustNotBeNull == null) {  &#xA;        throw new NullPointerException(&quot;mustNotBeNull must not be null&quot;);  &#xA;    }  &#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Whatever you do, don't allow a bad value to get set and throw an exception later when other code attempts to use it. That makes debugging a nightmare. You should always the follow the &quot;fail-fast&quot; principle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="758" LastEditorUserId="627727" LastEditDate="2015-11-03T21:39:35.567" LastActivityDate="2015-11-03T21:39:35.567" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="6392" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6496" CreationDate="2008-08-08T21:24:01.490" Score="23" ViewCount="25650" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am running a Tomcat application, and I need to display some time values.  Unfortunately, the time is coming up an hour off.  I looked into it and discovered that my default TimeZone is being set to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;sun.util.calendar.ZoneInfo[id=&quot;GMT-08:00&quot;,&#xA;                           offset=-28800000,&#xA;                           dstSavings=0,&#xA;                           useDaylight=false,&#xA;                           transitions=0,&#xA;                           lastRule=null]&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Rather than the Pacific time zone.  This is further indicated when I try to print the default time zone's &lt;a href=&quot;http://docs.oracle.com/javase/7/docs/api/java/util/TimeZone.html#getDisplayName()&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;display name&lt;/a&gt;, and it comes up &quot;GMT-08:00&quot;, which seems to indicate to me that it is not correctly set to the US Pacific time zone.  I am running on Ubuntu Hardy Heron, upgraded from Gutsy Gibbon.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there a configuration file I can update to tell the JRE to use Pacific with all the associated daylight savings time information?  The time on my machine shows correctly, so it doesn't seem to be an OS-wide misconfiguration.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ok, here's an update. A coworker suggested I update JAVA_OPTS in my /etc/profile to include &quot;-Duser.timezone=US/Pacific&quot;, which worked (I also saw CATALINA_OPTS, which I updated as well). Actually, I just exported the change into the variables rather than use the new /etc/profile (a reboot later will pick up the changes and I will be golden).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, I still think there is a better solution... there should be a configuration for Java somewhere that says what timezone it is using, or how it is grabbing the timezone. If someone knows such a setting, that would be awesome, but for now this is a decent workaround.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am using 1.5, and it is most definitely a DST problem.  As you can see, the time zone is set to not use daylight savings.  My belief is it is generically set to -8 offset rather than the specific Pacific timezone.  Since the generic -8 offset has no daylight savings info, it's of course not using it, but the question is, where do I tell Java to use Pacific time zone when it starts up?  I'm NOT looking for a programmatic solution, it should be a configuration solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastEditorUserId="2921691" LastEditorDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditDate="2016-02-07T18:06:11.540" LastActivityDate="2016-02-07T18:06:11.540" Title="Java Time Zone is messed up" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;linux&gt;&lt;timezone&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="10" />
<row Id="6397" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6392" CreationDate="2008-08-08T21:31:08.980" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Hmm... off by one hour. DST possibly?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is the date set correctly? &#xA;What version of the JDK is this running on? (&quot;java -version&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="758" LastActivityDate="2008-08-08T21:31:08.980" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6496" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6392" CreationDate="2008-08-09T00:46:46.260" Score="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's a &quot;quirk&quot; in the way the JVM looks up the zoneinfo file.  See &lt;a href=&quot;http://bugs.sun.com/bugdatabase/view_bug.do?bug_id=6456628&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Bug ID 6456628&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The easiest workaround is to make /etc/localtime a symlink to the correct zoneinfo file.  For Pacific time, the following commands should work:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;# sudo cp /etc/localtime /etc/localtime.dist&#xA;# sudo ln -fs /usr/share/zoneinfo/America/Los_Angeles /etc/localtime&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I haven't had any problems with the symlink approach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Edit: Added &quot;sudo&quot; to the commands.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="737" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T00:46:46.260" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="6502" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6392" CreationDate="2008-08-09T01:01:17.587" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;It may help to double-check the timezone rules your OS is using.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;/usr/bin/zdump -v /etc/localtime | less&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This file should contain your daylight savings rules, like this one for the year 2080:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;/etc/localtime  Sun Mar 31 01:00:00 2080 UTC = Sun Mar 31 02:00:00 2080 BST isdst=1 gmtoff=3600&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can compare this with the timezone rules you think you should be using. They can be found in &lt;strong&gt;/usr/share/zoneinfo/&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="304" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T01:01:17.587" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6612" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6655" CreationDate="2008-08-09T04:29:42.190" Score="35" ViewCount="26359" Body="&lt;p&gt;On a recent Java project, we needed a free Java based real-time data plotting utility.  After much searching, we found this tool called the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.epic.noaa.gov/java/sgt/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Scientific Graphics Toolkit or SGT&lt;/a&gt; from NOAA.  It seemed pretty robust, but we found out that it wasn't terribly configurable.  Or at least not configurable enough to meet our needs.  We ended up digging very deeply into the Java code and reverse engineering the code and changing it all around to make the plot tool look and act the way we wanted it to look and act.  Of course, this killed any chance for future upgrades from NOAA.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So what free or cheap Java based data plotting tools or libraries do you use?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Followup:  Thanks for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JFreeChart&lt;/a&gt; suggestions.  I checked out their website and it looks like a very nice data charting and plotting utility.  I should have made it clear in my original question that I was looking specifically to plot real-time data.  I corrected my question above to make that point clear.  It appears that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/faq.html#FAQ5&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JFreeChart support for live data is marginal at best, though&lt;/a&gt;.  Any other suggestions out there?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="27687" OwnerDisplayName="Kurt Leucht" LastEditorUserId="4370109" LastEditorDisplayName="Kurt Leucht" LastEditDate="2015-10-18T15:17:01.160" LastActivityDate="2015-10-18T15:17:01.160" Title="Are there any decent free Java data plotting libraries out there?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;plot&gt;&lt;configuration&gt;&lt;freeware&gt;" AnswerCount="16" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="16" ClosedDate="2013-01-04T22:05:01.957" />
<row Id="6639" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2008-08-09T05:33:22.967" Score="54" ViewCount="107907" Body="&lt;p&gt;How should I load files into my Java application?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="816" LastEditorUserId="1737819" LastEditDate="2014-01-30T07:11:29.327" LastActivityDate="2016-02-07T18:00:58.917" Title="How should I load files into my Java application?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;file&gt;&lt;loading&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="21" />
<row Id="6640" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6639" CreationDate="2008-08-09T05:35:50.623" Score="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The short answer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use one of these two methods:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/lang/Class.html#getResource(java.lang.String)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Class.getResource(String)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/lang/Class.html#getResourceAsStream(java.lang.String)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Class.getResourceAsStream(String)&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;InputStream inputStream = YourClass.class.getResourceAsStream(&quot;image.jpg&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The long answer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Typically, one would not want to load files using absolute paths. For example, dont do this if you can help it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;File file = new File(&quot;C:\\Users\\Joe\\image.jpg&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This technique is not recommended for at least two reasons. First, it creates a dependency on a particular operating system, which prevents the application from easily moving to another operating system. One of Javas main benefits is the ability to run the same bytecode on many different platforms. Using an absolute path like this makes the code much less portable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Second, depending on the relative location of the file, this technique might create an external dependency and limit the applications mobility. If the file exists outside the applications current directory, this creates an external dependency and one would have to be aware of the dependency in order to move the application to another machine (error prone).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead, use the &lt;code&gt;getResource()&lt;/code&gt; methods in the &lt;code&gt;Class&lt;/code&gt; class. This makes the application much more portable. It  can be moved to different platforms, machines, or directories and still function correctly.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="816" LastEditorUserId="2921691" LastEditorDisplayName="Justin Standard" LastEditDate="2016-02-07T18:00:58.917" LastActivityDate="2016-02-07T18:00:58.917" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="6648" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6612" CreationDate="2008-08-09T05:52:00.340" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I used JFreeChart (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/&lt;/a&gt;) on a previous project.  It has some very good built-in capabilities, and the design was WAY extensible so you could always roll your own extension later if you needed some custom chart annotation or wanted an axis to render differently, or whatever.  It's definitely worth checking out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="404" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T05:52:00.340" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6655" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6612" CreationDate="2008-08-09T06:23:19.140" Score="15" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've had success using &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JFreeChart&lt;/a&gt; on multiple projects. It is &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; configurable. JFreeChart is open source, but they charge for the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/devguide.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;developer guide&lt;/a&gt;. If you're doing something simple, the sample code is probably good enough. Otherwise, $50 for the developer guide is a pretty good bargain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With respect to &quot;real-time&quot; data, I've also used JFreeChart for these sorts of applications. Unfortunately, I had to create some custom data models with appropriate synchronization mechanisms to avoid race conditions. However, it wasn't terribly difficult and JFreeChart would still be my first choice. However, as the FAQ suggests, JFreeChart might not give you the best performance if that is a big concern.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="816" LastEditorUserId="816" LastEditorDisplayName="Will" LastEditDate="2008-08-09T20:46:36.900" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T20:46:36.900" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="6658" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6671" CreationDate="2008-08-09T06:31:25.283" Score="96" ViewCount="28310" Body="&lt;p&gt;At work we are currently still using JUnit 3 to run our tests. We have been considering switching over to JUnit 4 for &lt;strong&gt;new&lt;/strong&gt; tests being written but I have been keeping an eye on TestNG for a while now. What experiences have you all had with either JUnit 4 or TestNG, and which seems to work better for very large numbers of tests? Having flexibility in writing tests is also important to us since our functional tests cover a wide aspect and need to be written in a variety of ways to get results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Old tests will not be re-written as they do their job just fine. What I would like to see in new tests though is flexibility in the way the test can be written, natural assertions, grouping, and easily distributed test executions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="782" LastEditorUserId="2446208" LastEditorDisplayName="Sam Merrell" LastEditDate="2016-06-09T22:21:36.917" LastActivityDate="2016-06-29T22:38:50.827" Title="JUnit vs TestNG" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;testing&gt;&lt;junit&gt;&lt;testng&gt;" AnswerCount="12" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="25" />
<row Id="6659" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6658" CreationDate="2008-08-09T06:33:50.787" Score="19" Body="&lt;p&gt;First I would say, don't rewrite all your tests just to suit the latest fad.  Junit3 works perfectly well, and the introduction of annotations in 4 doesn't buy you very much (in my opinion).  It is much more important that you guys &lt;em&gt;write&lt;/em&gt; tests, and it sounds like you do.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use whatever seems most natural and helps you get your work done.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I can't comment on TestNG b/c I haven't used it.  But I would recommend &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.unitils.org/summary.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;unitils&lt;/a&gt;, a great wrapper for JUnit/TestNG/DBUnit/EasyMock, regardless of which route you take. (It supports all the flavors mentioned above)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="92" LastEditorUserId="92" LastEditorDisplayName="Justin Standard" LastEditDate="2008-09-10T22:46:22.533" LastActivityDate="2008-09-10T22:46:22.533" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="6671" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6658" CreationDate="2008-08-09T07:00:34.087" Score="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've used both, but I have to agree with Justin Standard that you shouldn't really consider rewriting your existing tests to any new format.  Regardless of the decision, it is pretty trivial to run both.  TestNG strives to be much more configurable than JUnit, but in the end they both work equally well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TestNG has a neat feature where you can mark tests as a particular group, and then easily run all tests of a specific group, or exclude tests of a particular group.  Thus you can mark tests that run slowly as in the &quot;slow&quot; group and then ignore them when you want quick results.  A suggestion from their documentation is to mark some subset as &quot;checkin&quot; tests which should be run whenever you check new files in.  I never saw such a feature in JUnit, but then again, if you don't have it, you don't REALLY miss it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For all its claims of high configuration, I did run into a corner case the a couple weeks ago where I couldn't do what I wanted to do... I wish I could remember what it is, but I wanted to bring it up so you know that it's not perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The biggest advantage TestNG has is annotations... which JUnit added in version 4 anyways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T07:00:34.087" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="6679" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6639" CreationDate="2008-08-09T07:18:04.550" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;getResource is fine, but using relative paths will work just as well too, as long as you can control where your working directory is (which you usually can).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore the platform dependence regarding the separator character can be gotten around using &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/io/File.html#separator&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;File.separator&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/io/File.html#separatorChar&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;File.separatorChar&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/lang/System.html#getProperties()&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;System.getProperty(&quot;file.separator&quot;)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T07:18:04.550" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="6683" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6612" CreationDate="2008-08-09T07:41:29.310" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've used &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jfree.org/jfreechart/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JFreeChart&lt;/a&gt; in a rather complex application that needed to visualize data streams and calculations based on the data. We implemented the ability to visually edit the data plots by mouse and had a very large set of data points. JFreeChart handled it very well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I was stuck with v0.7, but the newest release are sooo much better when it comes to API clarity. The community is very helpful and the developers are responding to mails too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you're doing a web application and don't want to bother with libraries, you can check the &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/apis/chart/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Google Chart API&lt;/a&gt;. Didn't use it myself, but I started some tests which were very promising.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="834" LastEditorUserId="1288" LastEditorDisplayName="Bill the Lizard" LastEditDate="2009-01-19T20:36:26.253" LastActivityDate="2009-01-19T20:36:26.253" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6687" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5855" CreationDate="2008-08-09T07:50:31.647" Score="4" Body="&lt;p&gt;I haven't done this before, but I found &lt;a href=&quot;http://i-proving.com/space/RCP+and+Java+Web+Start&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;this site&lt;/a&gt; on the web giving an explanation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastEditorUserId="23354" LastEditDate="2012-05-30T21:23:23.267" LastActivityDate="2012-05-30T21:23:23.267" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6708" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6639" CreationDate="2008-08-09T09:16:10.023" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I haven't had a problem just using unix-style path separators, even on Windows (though it is good practice to check &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.4.2/docs/api/java/io/File.html#separatorChar&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;File.separatorChar&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The technique of using &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.4.2/docs/api/java/lang/ClassLoader.html#getResource(java.lang.String)&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;ClassLoader.getResource()&lt;/a&gt; is best for read-only resources that are going to be loaded from JAR files. Sometimes, &lt;a href=&quot;http://illegalargumentexception.blogspot.com/2008/04/java-finding-application-directory.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;you can programmatically determine the application directory&lt;/a&gt;, which is useful for admin-configurable files or server applications. (Of course, user-editable files should be stored somewhere in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.4.2/docs/api/index.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;System.getProperty(&quot;user.home&quot;)&lt;/a&gt; directory.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="304" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T09:16:10.023" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="6713" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6658" CreationDate="2008-08-09T09:33:28.257" Score="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;About a year ago, we had the same problem. I spent sometime considering which move was better, and eventually we realized that TestNG has no 'killer features'. It's nice, and has some features JUnit 4 doesn't have, but we don't need them.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;We didn't want people to feel uncomfortable writing tests while getting to know TestNG because we wanted them to keep writing a lot of tests.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Also, JUnit is pretty much the de-facto standard in the Java world. There's no decent tool that doesn't support it from the box, you can find a lot of help on the web and they added a lot of new features in the past year which shows it's alive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We decided to stick with JUnit and never looked back.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="573" LastEditorUserId="573" LastEditDate="2010-09-28T07:30:46.077" LastActivityDate="2010-09-28T07:30:46.077" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6726" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="123" CreationDate="2008-08-09T11:06:58.973" Score="20" Body="&lt;p&gt;I know you asked for Java, but this strikes me as a task well suited to a scripting language. Here is a quick (very simple) solution written in Groovy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;test.csv&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;string,float1,float2,integer&#xA;hello world,1.0,3.3,4&#xA;goodbye world,1e9,-3.3,45&#xA;hello again,-1,23.33,456&#xA;hello world 3,1.40,34.83,4999&#xA;hello 2 world,9981.05,43.33,444&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;csvtoxml.groovy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;#!/usr/bin/env groovy&#xA;&#xA;def csvdata = []&#xA;new File(&quot;test.csv&quot;).eachLine { line -&amp;gt;&#xA;    csvdata &amp;lt;&amp;lt; line.split(',')&#xA;}&#xA;&#xA;def headers = csvdata[0]&#xA;def dataRows = csvdata[1..-1]&#xA;&#xA;def xml = new groovy.xml.MarkupBuilder()&#xA;&#xA;// write 'root' element&#xA;xml.root {&#xA;    dataRows.eachWithIndex { dataRow, index -&amp;gt;&#xA;        // write 'entry' element with 'id' attribute&#xA;        entry(id:index+1) {&#xA;            headers.eachWithIndex { heading, i -&amp;gt;&#xA;                // write each heading with associated content&#xA;                &quot;${heading}&quot;(dataRow[i])&#xA;            }&#xA;        }&#xA;    }&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Writes the following XML to stdout:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;root&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;entry id='1'&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;hello world&amp;lt;/string&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float1&amp;gt;1.0&amp;lt;/float1&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float2&amp;gt;3.3&amp;lt;/float2&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt;4&amp;lt;/integer&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/entry&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;entry id='2'&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;goodbye world&amp;lt;/string&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float1&amp;gt;1e9&amp;lt;/float1&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float2&amp;gt;-3.3&amp;lt;/float2&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt;45&amp;lt;/integer&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/entry&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;entry id='3'&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;hello again&amp;lt;/string&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float1&amp;gt;-1&amp;lt;/float1&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float2&amp;gt;23.33&amp;lt;/float2&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt;456&amp;lt;/integer&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/entry&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;entry id='4'&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;hello world 3&amp;lt;/string&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float1&amp;gt;1.40&amp;lt;/float1&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float2&amp;gt;34.83&amp;lt;/float2&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt;4999&amp;lt;/integer&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/entry&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;entry id='5'&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;string&amp;gt;hello 2 world&amp;lt;/string&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float1&amp;gt;9981.05&amp;lt;/float1&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;float2&amp;gt;43.33&amp;lt;/float2&amp;gt;&#xA;    &amp;lt;integer&amp;gt;444&amp;lt;/integer&amp;gt;&#xA;  &amp;lt;/entry&amp;gt;&#xA;&amp;lt;/root&amp;gt;&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, the code does very simple parsing (not taking into account quoted or escaped commas) and it does not account for possible absent data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="488" LastEditorUserId="395659" LastEditDate="2013-02-07T10:37:12.147" LastActivityDate="2013-02-07T10:37:12.147" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="6765" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6902" CreationDate="2008-08-09T13:23:40.617" Score="10" ViewCount="2315" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm going to start a new project - rewriting an existing system (PHP + SQL Server) from scratch because of some very serious limitations by design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have some quite good knowledge of SQL Server (currently we're using SQL Server 2000 in existing system) and we would like to employ its newer version (2008 I guess) in our new project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am really fond of technologies that Java offers - particularly Spring Framework and Wicket and I am quite familiar with Java from others projects and assignments before.&#xA;Therefore, we consider using Java and Microsoft SQL Server.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are two JDBC drivers for SQL Server - jTDS and Microsoft's one - &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/data/aa937724.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/data/aa937724.aspx&lt;/a&gt;. I think we should test both of them.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are there any limitations in such solution I should know of? Has someone experience with such a technology combination?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="837" LastEditorUserId="13302" LastEditDate="2010-11-04T07:17:05.780" LastActivityDate="2016-07-29T17:21:30.777" Title="Java + SQL Server - a viable solution?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;sql-server&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6779" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6765" CreationDate="2008-08-09T13:58:38.453" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't know about Java and 2008... but you shouldn't have too much trouble with Java and SQL2000. As lubos suggested, you'd be doing yourself a favour to look at c# but if you're much more comfortable with Java then there shouldn't be any real limitations as the JDBC connector &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/data/aa937724.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;is supported by Microsoft&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="493" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T13:58:38.453" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="6816" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="6840" CreationDate="2008-08-09T15:40:30.357" Score="63" ViewCount="25106" Body="&lt;p&gt;I was hoping someone could help me out with a problem I'm having using the java search function in Eclipse on a particular project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When using the java search on one particular project, I get an error message saying &lt;code&gt;Class file name must end with .class&lt;/code&gt; (see stack trace below). This does not seem to be happening on all projects, just one particular one, so perhaps there's something I should try to get rebuilt?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have already tried &lt;code&gt;Project -&amp;gt; Clean&lt;/code&gt;... and Closing Eclipse, deleting all the built class files and restarting Eclipse to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The only reference I've been able to find on Google for the problem is at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.crazysquirrel.com/computing/java/eclipse/error-during-java-search.jspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.crazysquirrel.com/computing/java/eclipse/error-during-java-search.jspx&lt;/a&gt;, but unfortunately his solution (closing, deleting class files, restarting) did not work for me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If anyone can suggest something to try, or there's any more info I can gather which might help track it's down, I'd greatly appreciate the pointers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Version: 3.4.0&#xA;Build id: I20080617-2000&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also just found this thread - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.myeclipseide.com/PNphpBB2-viewtopic-t-20067.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.myeclipseide.com/PNphpBB2-viewtopic-t-20067.html&lt;/a&gt; - which indicates the same problem may occur when the project name contains a period. Unfortunately, that's not the case in my setup, so I'm still stuck.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Caused by: java.lang.IllegalArgumentException: Class file name must end with .class&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.PackageFragment.getClassFile(PackageFragment.java:182)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.util.HandleFactory.createOpenable(HandleFactory.java:109)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.search.matching.MatchLocator.locateMatches(MatchLocator.java:1177)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.search.JavaSearchParticipant.locateMatches(JavaSearchParticipant.java:94)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.search.BasicSearchEngine.findMatches(BasicSearchEngine.java:223)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.search.BasicSearchEngine.search(BasicSearchEngine.java:506)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.core.search.SearchEngine.search(SearchEngine.java:551)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.corext.refactoring.RefactoringSearchEngine.internalSearch(RefactoringSearchEngine.java:142)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.corext.refactoring.RefactoringSearchEngine.search(RefactoringSearchEngine.java:129)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.corext.refactoring.rename.RenameTypeProcessor.initializeReferences(RenameTypeProcessor.java:594)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.corext.refactoring.rename.RenameTypeProcessor.doCheckFinalConditions(RenameTypeProcessor.java:522)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.corext.refactoring.rename.JavaRenameProcessor.checkFinalConditions(JavaRenameProcessor.java:45)&#xA;at org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring.participants.ProcessorBasedRefactoring.checkFinalConditions(ProcessorBasedRefactoring.java:225)&#xA;at org.eclipse.ltk.core.refactoring.Refactoring.checkAllConditions(Refactoring.java:160)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.refactoring.RefactoringExecutionHelper$Operation.run(RefactoringExecutionHelper.java:77)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.BatchOperation.executeOperation(BatchOperation.java:39)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.core.JavaModelOperation.run(JavaModelOperation.java:709)&#xA;at org.eclipse.core.internal.resources.Workspace.run(Workspace.java:1800)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.core.JavaCore.run(JavaCore.java:4650)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jdt.internal.ui.actions.WorkbenchRunnableAdapter.run(WorkbenchRunnableAdapter.java:92)&#xA;at org.eclipse.jface.operation.ModalContext$ModalContextThread.run(ModalContext.java:121)&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks McDowell, closing and opening the project seems to have fixed it (at least for now).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="797" LastEditorUserId="814074" LastEditorDisplayName="Matt Sheppard" LastEditDate="2013-12-23T08:14:44.977" LastActivityDate="2013-12-23T08:14:44.977" Title="Class file name must end with .class exception in Java Search" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;eclipse&gt;&lt;search&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="18" />
<row Id="6840" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6816" CreationDate="2008-08-09T16:31:32.623" Score="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;Two more general-purpose mechanisms for fixing some of Eclipse's idiosyncrasies:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Close and open the project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Delete the project (but not from disk!) and reimport it as an existing project&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Failing that, &lt;a href=&quot;https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=specific&amp;amp;order=relevance+desc&amp;amp;bug_status=__all__&amp;amp;product=JDT&amp;amp;content=Class+file+name+must+end+with+.class&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;bugs.eclipse.org&lt;/a&gt; might provide the answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the workspace is caching something broken, you may be able to delete it by poking around in &lt;strong&gt;workspace/.metadata/.plugins&lt;/strong&gt;. Most of that stuff is fairly transient (though backup and watch for deleted preferences).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="304" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T16:31:32.623" CommentCount="6" />
<row Id="6902" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6765" CreationDate="2008-08-09T20:18:15.240" Score="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've worked on a project using MSQL Server in conjunction with a Java Stack. It works very well and as long, since JDBC shouldn't really care about your database. We used ehcache together with Hibernate and had problems with the MS JDBC Driver, so we switched to jtds and it works really good.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's quite a while ago, so you still might wanna give the MS driver a chance...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastActivityDate="2008-08-09T20:18:15.240" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7076" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2092" CreationDate="2008-08-10T07:19:47.650" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is your scripting language bytecode generating? Does it generate debug metadata? If so, bytecode instrumentation is probably the way to go. In fact existing tools like will probably work; perhaps with minimal modification (the typical problem is the tools are written to work with Java and assume com.foo.Bar.class corresponds to com/foo/Bar.java. Unwinding that assumption can be tedious.) &lt;a href=&quot;http://emma.sourceforge.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;EMMA&lt;/a&gt; is a ClassLoader that does byte-code re-writing for code-coverage collection in Java. The coding style is a little funky, but I recommend reading the source for some ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your scripting language is interpreted then you will need something higher-level (source level) that hooks into the interpreter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="878" LastActivityDate="2008-08-10T07:19:47.650" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7083" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4242" CreationDate="2008-08-10T07:32:41.587" Score="13" Body="&lt;p&gt;One other way to do it is to use:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;String.valueOf(myInt);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This method is overloaded for every primitive type and &lt;code&gt;Object&lt;/code&gt;. This way you don't even have to think about the type you're using. Implementations of the method will call the appropriate method of the given type for you, e.g. &lt;code&gt;Integer.toString(myInt)&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/lang/String.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/lang/String.html&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="883" LastActivityDate="2008-08-10T07:32:41.587" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7269" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="46902" CreationDate="2008-08-10T18:06:04.820" Score="6" ViewCount="1433" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm part of a team that develops a pretty big Swing Java Applet. Most of our code are legacy and there are tons of singleton references. We've bunched all of them to a single &quot;Application Context&quot; singleton. What we now need is to create some way to separate the shared context (shared across all applets currently showing) and non-shared context (specific to each applet currently showing). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, we don't have an ID at each of the locations that call to the singleton, nor do we want to propagate the ID to all locations. What's the easiest way to identify in which applet context we're running? (I've tried messing with classloaders, thread groups, thread ids... so far I could find nothing that will enable me to ID the origin of the call).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="931" OwnerDisplayName="Ran Biron" LastEditorUserId="407418" LastEditDate="2016-03-11T17:58:30.780" LastActivityDate="2016-03-11T17:58:30.780" Title="How can I identify in which Java Applet context running without passing an ID?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;swing&gt;&lt;applet&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7539" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7561" CreationDate="2008-08-11T05:23:02.427" Score="37" ViewCount="41404" Body="&lt;p&gt;Recently I tried understanding the use of &lt;strong&gt;java.math.MathContext&lt;/strong&gt; but failed to understand properly. Is it used for rounding in &lt;code&gt;java.math.BigDecimal&lt;/code&gt;, if yes why does not it round the decimal digits but even mentissa part.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;From API docs, I came to know that it follows the standard specified in &lt;code&gt;ANSI X3.274-1996&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;ANSI X3.274-1996/AM 1-2000&lt;/code&gt; specifications but I did not get them to read online.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please let me know if you have any idea on this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="959" LastEditorUserId="1245337" LastEditDate="2014-11-25T07:17:29.357" LastActivityDate="2015-12-23T10:09:10.810" Title="Use of java.math.MathContext" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;math&gt;&lt;bigdecimal&gt;&lt;mathcontext&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="3" />
<row Id="7550" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7539" CreationDate="2008-08-11T05:44:00.747" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I'm understanding you correctly, it sounds like you're expecting the MathContext to control how many digits should be kept after the decimal point.  That's not what it's for.  It specifies how many digits to keep, &lt;em&gt;total&lt;/em&gt;.  So if you specify that you want 3 significant digits, that's all you're going to get.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;1234567890.123456789&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(20)));&#xA;&#xA;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;1234567890.123456789&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(10)));&#xA;&#xA;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;1234567890.123456789&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(5)));&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;will output:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1234567890.123456789&#xA;1234567890&#xA;1.2346E+9&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="872" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T05:44:00.747" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="7552" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7539" CreationDate="2008-08-11T05:45:35.173" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's not for fun. Actually I found some online example, which stated the use of &lt;code&gt;MathContext&lt;/code&gt; to round the amounts/numbers stored in BigDecimal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If &lt;code&gt;MathContext&lt;/code&gt; is configured to have &lt;code&gt;precision = 2&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;rounding mode = ROUND_HALF_EVEN&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;BigDecimal Number = 0.5294&lt;/code&gt;, is &lt;em&gt;rounded&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;strong&gt;0.53&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I thought it is a newer technique and used it for rounding purpose. However it turned into nightmare because it started rounding even mentissa part of number.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Number = 1.5294&lt;/code&gt; is rounded to &lt;code&gt;1.5&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Number = 10.5294&lt;/code&gt; is rounded to &lt;code&gt;10&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;Number = 101.5294&lt;/code&gt; is rounded to &lt;code&gt;100&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;.... and so on&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So this is not the behavior I expected for rounding (as precision = 2).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It seems to be having some logic because from patter I can say that it takes first two digits (as precision is 2) of number and then appends 0's till the no. of digits become same as unrounded amount (checkout the example of 101.5294 ...)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="959" LastEditorUserId="113962" LastEditDate="2015-12-23T10:09:10.810" LastActivityDate="2015-12-23T10:09:10.810" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="7557" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5527" CreationDate="2008-08-11T05:56:14.730" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Instead of J#, I would rather prefer IKVM (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ikvm.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.ikvm.net/&lt;/a&gt;) to convert my JARs to .NET assemblies as well as access Java APIs in C#.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="959" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T05:56:14.730" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7561" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7539" CreationDate="2008-08-11T06:06:48.483" Score="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;@jatan&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Thanks for you answer. It makes sense. Can you please explain me MathContext in the context of BigDecimal#round method.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's nothing special about &lt;code&gt;BigDecimal.round()&lt;/code&gt; &lt;em&gt;vs.&lt;/em&gt; any other &lt;code&gt;BigDecimal&lt;/code&gt; method.  In all cases, the &lt;code&gt;MathContext&lt;/code&gt; specifies the number of significant digits and the rounding technique.  Basically, there are two parts of every &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/math/MathContext.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;MathContext&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.  There's a precision, and there's also a &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/math/RoundingMode.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;RoundingMode&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The precision again specifies the number of significant digits.  So if you specify &lt;code&gt;123&lt;/code&gt; as a number, and ask for 2 significant digits, you're going to get &lt;code&gt;120&lt;/code&gt;.  It might be clearer if you think in terms of scientific notation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;123&lt;/code&gt; would be &lt;code&gt;1.23e2&lt;/code&gt; in scientific notation.  If you only keep 2 significant digits, then you get &lt;code&gt;1.2e2&lt;/code&gt;, or &lt;code&gt;120&lt;/code&gt;.  By reducing the number of significant digits, we reduce the precision with which we can specify a number.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;code&gt;RoundingMode&lt;/code&gt; part specifies how we should handle the loss of precision.  To reuse the example, if you use &lt;code&gt;123&lt;/code&gt; as the number, and ask for 2 significant digits, you've reduced your precision.  With a &lt;code&gt;RoundingMode&lt;/code&gt; of &lt;code&gt;HALF_UP&lt;/code&gt; (the default mode), &lt;code&gt;123&lt;/code&gt; will become &lt;code&gt;120&lt;/code&gt;.  With a &lt;code&gt;RoundingMode&lt;/code&gt; of &lt;code&gt;CEILING&lt;/code&gt;, you'll get &lt;code&gt;130&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;123.4&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(4,RoundingMode.HALF_UP)));&#xA;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;123.4&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(2,RoundingMode.HALF_UP)));&#xA;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;123.4&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(2,RoundingMode.CEILING)));&#xA;System.out.println(new BigDecimal(&quot;123.4&quot;,&#xA;                   new MathContext(1,RoundingMode.CEILING)));&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Outputs:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;123.4&#xA;1.2E+2&#xA;1.3E+2&#xA;2E+2&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can see that both the precision and the rounding mode affect the output.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="872" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T06:06:48.483" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7596" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="13283" CreationDate="2008-08-11T07:45:20.050" Score="30" ViewCount="11273" Body="&lt;p&gt;First of all, I know how to build a Java application. But I have always been puzzled about where to put my classes. There are proponents for organizing the packages in a strictly domain oriented fashion, others separate by tier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I myself have always had problems with a) with naming, b) with placing&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where do you put your domain specific constants (and what is the best name for such a class)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where do you put classes for stuff which is both infrastructural and domain specific (for instance I have a FileStorageStrategy class, which stores the files either in the database, or alternatively in database)?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Where to put Exceptions?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are there any standards to which I can refer?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="917" LastEditorUserId="1743880" LastEditDate="2015-12-14T13:24:57.390" LastActivityDate="2016-01-27T05:38:47.867" Title="How should I structure a Java application, in other words: where do I put my classes?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;architecture&gt;" AnswerCount="10" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="10" CommunityOwnedDate="2009-08-29T17:41:21.030" />
<row Id="7599" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-11T08:00:58.830" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Class names should always be descriptive and self-explanatory. If you have multiple domains of responsibility for your classes then they should probably be refactored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Likewise for you packages. They should be grouped by domain of responsibility. Every domain has it's own exceptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Generally don't sweat it until you get to a point where it is becoming overwhelming and bloated. Then sit down and don't code, just refactor the classes out, compiling regularly to make sure everything works. Then continue as you did before.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="342" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T08:00:58.830" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7610" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-11T08:24:02.950" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Use packages to group related functionality together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Usually the top of your package tree is your domain name reversed (&lt;code&gt;com.domain.subdomain&lt;/code&gt;) to guarantee uniqueness, and then usually there will be a package for your application. Then subdivide that by related area, so your &lt;code&gt;FileStorageStrategy&lt;/code&gt; might go in, say, &lt;code&gt;com.domain.subdomain.myapp.storage&lt;/code&gt;, and then there might be specific implementations/subclasses/whatever in &lt;code&gt;com.domain.subdomain.myapp.storage.file&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;com.domain.subdomain.myapp.storage.database&lt;/code&gt;. These names can get pretty long, but &lt;code&gt;import&lt;/code&gt; keeps them all at the top of files and IDEs can help to manage that as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Exceptions usually go in the same package as the classes that throw them, so if you had, say, &lt;code&gt;FileStorageException&lt;/code&gt; it would go in the same package as &lt;code&gt;FileStorageStrategy&lt;/code&gt;. Likewise an interface defining constants would be in the same package.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's not really any standard as such, just use common sense, and if it all gets too messy, refactor!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="588" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T08:24:02.950" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7661" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="32551" CreationDate="2008-08-11T10:23:48.763" Score="6" ViewCount="18048" Body="&lt;p&gt;Searching for some sample code for converting a point in WGS84 coordinate system to a map position in Google Maps (pixel position), also supporting zoom levels. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If the codes is well commented, then it can also be in some other language.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also point me to a open source Java project :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some resources found:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://trac.openlayers.org/browser/trunk/openlayers/lib/OpenLayers/Layer&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;OpenLayer&lt;/a&gt; implementation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://josm.openstreetmap.de/browser/trunk/src/org/openstreetmap/josm/data/projection&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;JOSM&lt;/a&gt; project&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Excellent &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/OSUCartography/JMapProjLib&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Java Map Projection Library &lt;/a&gt; from JH LABS. This is a pure java PROJ.4 port. Does projection from WGS84 to meters. From there it's quite straightforward to convert meters to tile pixels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="706" LastEditorUserId="706" LastEditorDisplayName="JaanusSiim" LastEditDate="2016-06-13T10:14:14.240" LastActivityDate="2016-06-13T10:14:14.240" Title="Java code for WGS84 to Google map position and back" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;google-maps&gt;&lt;mapping&gt;&lt;wgs84&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="4" />
<row Id="7668" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7661" CreationDate="2008-08-11T10:58:11.080" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Someone took the javascript code from Google Maps and ported it to python: &lt;a href=&quot;http://code.google.com/p/gheat/source/browse/trunk/__/lib/python/gmerc.py&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;gmerc.py&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've used this and it works great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="309844" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T10:58:11.080" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7679" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7661" CreationDate="2008-08-11T11:29:18.113" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://geotools.codehaus.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;GeoTools&lt;/a&gt; has code to transform to and from about any coordinate system you could imagine, and among them also Google Map's. It's also open source. However, it should also be pointed out that GeoTools is a &lt;strong&gt;large&lt;/strong&gt; library, so if you're looking something small, quick and easy, it's likely not the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would highly recommend it though if you're going to do other GIS/coordinate transformations, etc. as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you use GeoTools or something similar, you might also be interested in knowing that the Google Map coordinate system is called EPSG 3785.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="890" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T11:29:18.113" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7681" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="7688" CreationDate="2008-08-11T11:33:01.930" Score="6" ViewCount="1499" Body="&lt;p&gt;What is the best way to verify/test that a text string is serialized to a byte array with a certain encoding?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my case, I want to verify that an XML structure is serialized to a byte array with the UTF-8 encoding which is of variable character length. As an example, my current ugly procedure is to inject a character known to require two bytes into the structure before serializing, then replacing the two-byte character with an ASCII character and comparing the serialized array lengths. This should yield two serialized arrays where the array containing the two-byte characters should have length +1.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Plus if the solution is elegant for Java. &#xA;I can't think of any elegant way to seek for a byte sequence in a byte array. (Could be used to seek for a known byte sequence representing the desired character representation in UTF-8.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="972" LastActivityDate="2013-01-09T05:53:18.357" Title="Test serialization encoding" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;xml&gt;&lt;string&gt;&lt;serialization&gt;&lt;encoding&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7688" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7681" CreationDate="2008-08-11T11:46:40.030" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Perhaps you could deserialise the byte array using a known encoding and ensure that (a) it doesn't throw any exceptions, and (b) deserialises to the original string. It seems that from your description of the scenario, you may not have the original string readily available. Might there be a way to create it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="893" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T11:46:40.030" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7698" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7681" CreationDate="2008-08-11T12:05:03.427" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;That's good.&#xA;You're right, I don't have the original string, since I'm testing a module that creates an XML document as a byte array. I didn't think about deserializing to a String with an expected encoding. That will do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="972" LastEditorUserId="1471203" LastEditDate="2013-01-09T05:53:18.357" LastActivityDate="2013-01-09T05:53:18.357" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7717" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7269" CreationDate="2008-08-11T12:32:02.480" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;If I understand you correctly, the idea is to get a different &quot;singleton&quot; object for each caller object or &quot;context&quot;.&#xA;One thing you can do is to create a thread-local global variable where you write the ID of the current context. (This can be done with AOP.) Then in the singleton getter, the context ID is fetched from the thread-local to use as a key to the correct &quot;singleton&quot; instance for the calling context. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Regarding AOP there should be no problem using it in applets since, depending on your point-cuts, the advices are woven at compile time and a JAR is added to the runtime dependencies. Hence, no special evidence of AOP should remain at run time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="972" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T12:32:02.480" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7720" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="149971" CreationDate="2008-08-11T12:37:50.503" Score="34" ViewCount="11694" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am writing an application in Java for the desktop using the Eclipse SWT library for GUI rendering.  I think SWT helps Java get over the biggest hurdle for acceptance on the desktop: namely providing a Java application with a consistent, responsive interface that looks like that belonging to any other app on your desktop.  However, I feel that packaging an application is still an issue.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;OS X natively provides an easy mechanism for wrapping Java apps in native application bundles, but producing an app for Windows/Linux that doesn't require the user to run an ugly batch file or click on a .jar is still a hassle.  Possibly that's not such an issue on Linux, where the user is likely to be a little more tech-savvy, but on Windows I'd like to have a regular .exe for him/her to run.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Has anyone had any experience with any of the .exe generation tools for Java that are out there?  I've tried JSmooth but had various issues with it.  Is there a better solution before I crack out Visual Studio and roll my own?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt;  I should perhaps mention that I am unable to spend a lot of money on a commercial solution.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="998" LastEditorUserId="56285" LastEditorDisplayName="alexmcchessers" LastEditDate="2010-04-26T11:02:03.770" LastActivityDate="2014-08-25T06:17:01.043" Title="Packaging Java apps for the Windows/Linux desktop" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;windows&gt;&lt;swt&gt;&lt;executable&gt;&lt;software-distribution&gt;" AnswerCount="18" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="25" />
<row Id="7747" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-11T12:59:04.550" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ej-technologies.com/products/install4j/overview.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Install4J&lt;/a&gt;. Not free, but worth it. Give the trial a shot&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="287" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T12:59:04.550" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="7759" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:09:20.330" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I went through the same and found that all of the free options weren't very good. Looks like you'll be writing your own. I'd be interested to see if someone has a free/cheap option that works&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="287" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T13:09:20.330" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7770" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:20:39.560" Score="-5" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you choose to throw a NPE and you are using the argument in your method, it might be redundant and expensive to explicitly check for a null. I think the VM already does that for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1009" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T13:20:39.560" CommentCount="3" />
<row Id="7779" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="28154" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:30:21.850" Score="8" ViewCount="2859" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have read through several reviews on Amazon and some books seem outdated.  I am currently using MyEclipse 6.5 which is using Eclipse 3.3.  I'm interested in hearing from people that have experience learning RCP and what reference material they used to get started.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="791" LastEditorUserId="275567" LastEditDate="2012-10-14T04:13:48.373" LastActivityDate="2012-10-14T04:13:48.373" Title="I would like a recommendation for a book on Eclipse's Rich Client Platform (RCP)" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;eclipse&gt;&lt;rcp&gt;&lt;myeclipse&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="7790" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7779" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:37:15.423" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Although I don't have personal experience, a few friends of mine did Eclipse RCP development, and they used the book &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0321334612&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Eclipse Rich Client Platform: Designing, Coding, and Packaging Java(TM) Applications&lt;/a&gt;&quot;. They seemed to like it a lot, and I looked it at myself, and it seemed useful. If I was going to do RCP development on Eclipse, I would probably get this book.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To clarify - this book is geared toward Eclipse 3.1, and since I haven't done any RCP development of my own, I'm not sure how much things have changed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="572" LastEditorUserId="572" LastEditorDisplayName="Thomas Owens" LastEditDate="2008-08-11T13:45:00.087" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T13:45:00.087" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7792" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7779" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:42:12.560" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I read the &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0321334612&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;book&lt;/a&gt; suggested by Thomas and it's really worth reading, although not very up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T13:42:12.560" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7796" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-11T13:48:31.593" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Have you thought about &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/technologies/desktop/javawebstart/index.jsp&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Java Web Start&lt;/a&gt;?  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ibm.com/developerworks/opensource/library/os-jws/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is a tutorial specifically for deploying an SWT application with Java Web Start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="737" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T13:48:31.593" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="7877" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6222" CreationDate="2008-08-11T15:42:36.747" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm using Eclipse with a 64bit VM. However I have to use Java 1.5, because with Java 1.6, even 1.6.0_10ea, Eclipse crashed when changing the .classpath-file. On Linux I had the same problems and could only get the 64bit Eclipse to work with 64bit Java 1.5.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The problem seems to be with the just in time compilation, since with vmparam -Xint eclipse works -- but this is not a sollution, because it's slow then.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With 1.6.0_11 it seems to work. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;1.6_10 final might work as well as mentioned in the comment, but I've not tested that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="969" LastEditorUserId="969" LastEditorDisplayName="Tobias Schulte" LastEditDate="2009-01-20T10:38:04.790" LastActivityDate="2009-01-20T10:38:04.790" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="8132" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-11T19:43:49.210" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;The accepted practice if to use the &lt;em&gt;IllegalArgumentException( String message )&lt;/em&gt; to declare a parameter to be invalid and give as much detail as possible... So to say that a parameters was found to be null while exception non-null, you would do something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;if( variable == null )&#xA;    throw new IllegalArgumentException(&quot;The object 'variable' cannot be null&quot;);&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You have virtually no reason to implicitly use the &quot;NullPointerException&quot;. The NullPointerException is an exception thrown by the Java Virtual Machine when you try to execute code on null reference (Like &lt;em&gt;toString()&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="244" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T19:43:49.210" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8160" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3881" CreationDate="2008-08-11T20:05:18.527" Score="124" Body="&lt;p&gt;The standard is to throw the NullPointerException. The generally infallible &quot;Effective Java&quot; discusses this briefly in Item 42 (in the first edition) or Item 60 (in the second edition) &quot;Favor the use of standard exceptions&quot;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&quot;Arguably, all erroneous method&#xA;  invocations boil down to an illegal&#xA;  argument or illegal state, but other&#xA;  exceptions are standardly used for&#xA;  certain kinds of illegal arguments and&#xA;  states. If a caller passes null in&#xA;  some parameter for which null values&#xA;  are prohibited, convention dictates&#xA;  that NullPointerException be thrown&#xA;  rather than IllegalArgumentException.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1035" LastEditorUserId="116509" LastEditDate="2013-10-23T11:39:47.297" LastActivityDate="2013-10-23T11:39:47.297" CommentCount="12" />
<row Id="8163" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7269" CreationDate="2008-08-11T20:06:28.070" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;@Hugo regarding threadlocal:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I thought about that solution. However, from experiments I found two problems with that approach:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shared thread (server connections, etc) are problematic. This can be solved though by paying special attention to these thread (they're all under my control and are pretty much isolated from the legacy code).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The EDT thread is shared across all applets. I failed to find a way to force the creation of a new EDT thread for each applet. This means that the threadlocal for the EDT would be shared across the applets. This one I have no idea how to solve. Suggestions?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="931" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T20:06:28.070" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="8219" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8226" CreationDate="2008-08-11T21:07:44.687" Score="7" ViewCount="336" Body="&lt;p&gt;At my work we are running a group of tests that consist of about 3,000 separate test cases. Previously we were running this entire test suite on one machine, which took about 24-72 hours to complete the entire test run. We now have created our own system for grouping and distributing the tests among about three separate machines and the tests are prioritized so that the core tests get run first for more immediate results and the extra tests run when there is an available machine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am curious if anyone has found a good way to distribute their tests among several machines to reduce total test time for a complete run and what tools were used to achieve that. I've done some research and it looks like TestNG is &lt;a href=&quot;http://beust.com/weblog/archives/000362.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;moving in this direction&lt;/a&gt;, but it looks like it is still under quite a bit of development. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We don't plan on rewriting any of our tests, but as we add new tests and test new products or add-ons I'd like to be able to deal with the fact that we are working with very large numbers of tests. On the other hand, if we can find a tool that would help distribute our Junit &lt;code&gt;3.x&lt;/code&gt; tests even in a very basic fashion, that &lt;em&gt;would&lt;/em&gt; be helpful since we wouldn't have to maintain our own tooling to do that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="782" LastEditorUserId="1584286" LastEditorDisplayName="Sam Merrell" LastEditDate="2013-07-04T12:08:44.800" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T03:58:10.860" Title="Test Distribution" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;testing&gt;&lt;enterprise&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="8226" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8219" CreationDate="2008-08-11T21:13:06.813" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen some people having a play with &lt;a href=&quot;http://216.93.179.140:8080/wiki/display/GG15UG/Distributed+JUnit+Overview&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;distributed JUnit&lt;/a&gt;. I can't particularly vouch for how effective it is, but the other teams I've seen seemed to think it was straight forward enough. Hope that helps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1035" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T21:13:06.813" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8274" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8219" CreationDate="2008-08-11T22:09:16.827" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Our build people use Mozilla Tinderbox.  It seems to have some hooks for distributed testing.  I'm sorry not to know the details but I thought I would at least pass on the pointer to you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's also nice coz you can find out immediately when a build breaks, and what checkin might have been the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mozilla.org/tinderbox.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.mozilla.org/tinderbox.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="116" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T22:09:16.827" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8307" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2931" CreationDate="2008-08-11T22:38:05.567" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;The META-INF.services stuff is known by its class name in the API: &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/6/docs/api/java/util/ServiceLoader.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;ServiceLoader&lt;/a&gt;. A Google search for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.google.ca/search?hl=en&amp;amp;q=ServiceLoader&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;ServiceLoader&lt;/a&gt; yields some information.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am not really familiar with it, but sometimes it's all about knowing the right search keywords.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1054" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T22:38:05.567" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8318" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8322" CreationDate="2008-08-11T22:53:50.883" Score="9" ViewCount="8228" Body="&lt;p&gt;I need to prevent &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.owasp.org/index.php/Session_Fixation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Session Fixation&lt;/a&gt;, a particular type of session hijacking, in a Java web application running in JBoss. However, it appears that the standard idiom &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.owasp.org/index.php/Session_Fixation_in_Java&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;doesn't work in JBoss&lt;/a&gt;. Can this be worked around?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1054" LastActivityDate="2013-05-21T09:36:53.937" Title="Resolving Session Fixation in JBoss" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;security&gt;&lt;jboss&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="5" />
<row Id="8322" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8318" CreationDate="2008-08-11T23:00:58.467" Score="6" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://jira.jboss.org/jira/browse/JBAS-4436&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;This defect&lt;/a&gt; (found &lt;a href=&quot;http://forum.springframework.org/showthread.php?t=54688&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) points the way to the solution. The Tomcat instance that runs in JBoss is configured with emptySessionPath=&quot;true&quot;, rather than &quot;false&quot;, which is the default. This can be modified in &lt;code&gt;.../deploy/jboss-web.deployer/server.xml&lt;/code&gt;; both the HTTP and AJP connectors have this option.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The feature itself is used to eliminate the context path (eg. &quot;foo&quot; in &lt;a href=&quot;http://example.com/foo&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://example.com/foo&lt;/a&gt;) from being included in the JSESSIONID cookie. Setting it to false will break applications that rely on cross-application authentication, which includes stuff built using some portal frameworks. It didn't negatively affect the application in question, however.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1054" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T23:00:58.467" CommentCount="2" />
<row Id="8335" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-11T23:25:44.503" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;One thing I've done in the past - if I'm extending a class I'll try and follow their conventions. For example, when working with the Spring Framework, I'll have my MVC Controller classes in a package called com.mydomain.myapp.web.servlet.mvc&#xA;If I'm not extending something I just go with what is simplest. com.mydomain.domain for Domain Objects (although if you have a ton of domain objects this package could get a bit unwieldy).&#xA;For domain specific constants, I actually put them as public constants in the most related class. For example, if I have a &quot;Member&quot; class and have a maximum member name length constant, I put it in the Member class. Some shops make a separate Constants class but I don't see the value in lumping unrelated numbers and strings into a single class. I've seen some other shops try to solve this problem by creating SEPARATE Constants classes, but that just seems like a waste of time and the result is too confusing. Using this setup, a large project with multiple developers will be duplicating constants all over the place.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="543" LastActivityDate="2008-08-11T23:25:44.503" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8400" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-12T01:28:23.287" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I like break my classes down into packages that are related to each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Model&lt;/strong&gt; For database related calls&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;View&lt;/strong&gt; Classes that deal with what you see&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Control&lt;/strong&gt; Core functionality classes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Util&lt;/strong&gt; Any misc. classes that are used (typically static functions)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="396" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T01:28:23.287" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8438" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-12T03:36:32.123" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think keep it simple and don't over think it. Don't over abstract and layer too much. Just keep it neat, and as it grows, refactoring it is trivial. One of the best features of IDEs is refactoring, so why not make use of it and save you brain power for solving problems that are related to your app, rather then meta issues like code organisation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="699" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T03:36:32.123" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8569" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="13367" CreationDate="2008-08-12T07:36:14.107" Score="22" ViewCount="9944" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm currently trying to get into the Java EE development with the Spring framework. As I'm new to Spring, it is hard to imaging how a good running project should start off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Do you have any &lt;em&gt;best practices&lt;/em&gt;, tipps or major &lt;em&gt;DO NOTs&lt;/em&gt; for a starter? How did you start with Spring - big project or small tutorial-like applications? Which technology did you use right away: AOP, complex Hibernate...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="834" LastEditorUserId="834" LastEditorDisplayName="cringe" LastEditDate="2008-08-12T07:55:11.243" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T03:59:25.720" Title="What's your &quot;best practice&quot; for the first Java EE Spring project?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;spring&gt;&lt;java-ee&gt;&lt;aop&gt;" AnswerCount="11" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="13" ClosedDate="2013-11-18T06:01:19.743" />
<row Id="8571" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T07:40:19.293" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;Whilst its been years since I have used spring, and I can't say I am a fan of it, I know that the App Fuse tool (&lt;a href=&quot;https://java.net/projects/appfuse/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;https://java.net/projects/appfuse/&lt;/a&gt;) has been helpful to help people bootstrap in terms of generating all the artifacts you need to get going.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="699" LastEditorUserId="1845869" LastEditDate="2013-11-26T03:58:58.803" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T03:58:58.803" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8576" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T07:43:24.153" Score="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;Focus first on the heart of Spring: Dependency Injection. Once you see all the ways that DI can be used, then start thinking about the more interesting pieces like AOP, Remoting, JDBC Templates etc. So my best bit of advice is let your use of Spring grow out from the core.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Best practice? If you're using the standard XML config, manage the size of individual files and comment them judiciously. You may think that you and others will perfectly understand your bean definitions, but in practice they're somewhat harder to come back to than plain old java code.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1035" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T07:43:24.153" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8586" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T07:54:25.023" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;I actually quite liked Spring.. It was a fresh breeze of air in your average J2EE Java Beans..&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I recommend implementing the example Spring provides: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://static.springframework.org/docs/Spring-MVC-step-by-step/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://static.springframework.org/docs/Spring-MVC-step-by-step/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, I decided to go full monty and added Hibernate to my Spring application ;), because Spring provides excellent support for Hibernate... :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do have a DON'T however, which I learned the hard way (product in production)... If you only implement the Controller interface, and return a ModelAndView object with some data as provided with the interface, Spring does garbadge collect those resources, for tries to cache those data. So be careful to put large data in those ModelAndView objects, because they will hog up your server memory for as long as the server is in the air as soon as that page has been viewed...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="900" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T07:54:25.023" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="8594" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7596" CreationDate="2008-08-12T08:00:18.707" Score="9" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm a huge fan of organized sources, so I always create the following directory structure:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;/src - for your packages &amp;amp; classes&#xA;/test - for unit tests&#xA;/docs - for documentation, generated and manually edited&#xA;/lib - 3rd party libraries&#xA;/etc - unrelated stuff&#xA;/bin (or /classes) - compiled classes, output of your compile&#xA;/dist - for distribution packages, hopefully auto generated by a build system&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In /src I'm using the default Java patterns: Package names starting with your domain (org.yourdomain.yourprojectname) and class names reflecting the OOP aspect you're creating with the class (see the other commenters). Common package names like &lt;em&gt;util&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;model&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;view&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;events&lt;/em&gt; are useful, too.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I tend to put constants for a specific topic in an own class, like &lt;em&gt;SessionConstants&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;ServiceConstants&lt;/em&gt; in the same package of the domain classes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="834" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T08:00:18.707" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8598" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-12T08:05:53.500" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;Maybe you should take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://izpack.org/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;IzPack&lt;/a&gt;. I created a very nice installer some years ago and I'd bet that they are still improving it. It allows the installation of docs, binaries and a clickable link to start the application &lt;em&gt;IIRC&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="834" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T08:05:53.500" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="8599" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="8655" CreationDate="2008-08-12T08:08:11.327" Score="7" ViewCount="1089" Body="&lt;p&gt;Can anyone recommend a good binary XML format? It's for a JavaME application, so it needs to be a) Easy to implement on the server, and b) Easy to write a low-footprint parser for on a low-end JavaME client device.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And it goes without saying that it needs to be smaller than XML, and faster to parse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The data would be something akin to SVG.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="974" LastEditorUserId="1288" LastEditDate="2012-04-12T11:14:22.717" LastActivityDate="2014-03-21T03:12:40.260" Title="Best binary XML format for JavaME" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;xml&gt;&lt;java-me&gt;&lt;mobile&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="0" />
<row Id="8602" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-12T08:15:51.093" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Have you considered writing a small program in C/C++ that just calls &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms682425.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;CreateProcess&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to start up the java VM with the jar (or class) file?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You could get &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.microsoft.com/express/vc/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Visual C++ Express&lt;/a&gt; and put together the startup program pretty easily.  This would make it easy to add a friendly icon as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="872" LastEditorUserId="872" LastEditorDisplayName="Derek Park" LastEditDate="2008-08-12T08:21:36.993" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T08:21:36.993" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8620" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7720" CreationDate="2008-08-12T08:55:33.150" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;Another option I was considering: rather than writing a native launcher from scratch, Eclipse comes with the source code for its own launcher, and this could perhaps be repurposed for my app.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's a shame that Sun never included anything similar in the JDK.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="998" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T08:55:33.150" CommentCount="1" />
<row Id="8635" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T09:31:41.737" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;A good way to get started is to concentrate on the &quot;Springframework&quot;. The Spring portfolio has grown to a big pile of projects around various aspects of Enterprise Software. Stick to the core at the beginning and try to grasp the concepts. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.springframework.org/download&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Download&lt;/a&gt; the latest binaries and check out Spring's petclinic example once you are familiar with the core. It gives quite a good overview of the various projects SpringSource has to offer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although the documentation is very good, &lt;a href=&quot;http://dlinsin.blogspot.com/2008/05/book-review-building-spring-2.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;I'd recommend a book&lt;/a&gt; after you grasp the concepts of the core. What I've found problematic with the documentation, is that it's not in depth and can't give you all the details you need.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" OwnerDisplayName="david" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T09:31:41.737" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8642" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T10:00:45.017" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Spring is also very much about unit testing and therefore testability of your classes. That basically means thinking about modularization, separation of concerns, referencing a class through interfaces etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="837" OwnerDisplayName="martinsb" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T10:00:45.017" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8645" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8599" CreationDate="2008-08-12T10:13:29.687" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;What kind of data are you planning to use? I would say, that if the server is also done in Java, easiest way for small footprint is to send/receive binary data in predefined format. Just write everything in known order into &lt;code&gt;DataOutputStream&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But it would really depend, what what kind of data are you working on and can you define the format.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Actually you should evaluate, if this kind of optimization is even needed. Maybe you target devices are not &lt;strong&gt;so&lt;/strong&gt; limited.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="706" OwnerDisplayName="JaanusSiim" LastEditorUserId="3330969" LastEditorDisplayName="JaanusSiim" LastEditDate="2014-03-21T03:12:40.260" LastActivityDate="2014-03-21T03:12:40.260" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8655" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8599" CreationDate="2008-08-12T10:42:35.917" Score="5" Body="&lt;p&gt;You might want to take a look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WBXML&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;wbxml&lt;/a&gt; (Wireless Binary XML) it is optimized for size, and often used on mobile phones, but it is not optimized for parsing speed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="238" OwnerDisplayName="Pat" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T10:42:35.917" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8967" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T15:28:59.940" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you're just looking to dabble in it a bit and see if you like it, I recommend starting with the DAO layer, using Spring's JDBC and/or Hibernate support. This will expose you to a lot of the core concepts, but do so in a way that is easy to isolate from the rest of your app. This is the route I followed, and it was good warm-up before getting into building a full application with Spring.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="765" OwnerDisplayName="Nicholas Trandem" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T15:28:59.940" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="8968" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="9404" CreationDate="2008-08-12T15:29:18.067" Score="7" ViewCount="520" Body="&lt;p&gt;We need to add WorkFlow to our Spring managed application. Does anyone have any useful experience in using any of the myriad of OSS Work Flow solutions? Which one is best? Which one integrates with Spring best? Which ones should we avoid?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1126" OwnerDisplayName="TiGz" LastActivityDate="2013-08-18T09:19:43.010" Title="What OSS project should I look at if I need to do Spring friendly WorkFlow?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;spring&gt;&lt;workflow&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9044" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="275353" CreationDate="2008-08-12T16:52:08.697" Score="10" ViewCount="7639" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have a base class that represents a database test in TestNG, and I want to specify that all classes extending from this class are of a group &quot;db-test&quot;, however I have found that this doesn't seem possible.  I have tried the @Test annotation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@Test(groups = { &quot;db-test&quot; })&#xA;public class DBTestBase {&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, this doesn't work because the @Test annotation will try to make a bunch of methods into tests, and warnings/errors pop up in eclipse when the tests are run.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So I tried disabling the test, so at least the groups are assigned:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;@Test(enabled = false, groups = { &quot;db-test&quot; })&#xA;public class DBTestBase {&#xA;}&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but then any @BeforeTest (and other similar annotations) ALSO get disabled... which is of course not what I want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would like some way to annotate a class as being of a particular type of group, but it doesn't quite seem possible in TestNG.  Does anyone have any other ideas?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditorUserId="6309" LastEditorDisplayName="VonC" LastEditDate="2008-11-08T22:51:50.377" LastActivityDate="2009-03-16T18:31:06.593" Title="Can I specify a class wide group on a TestNG test case?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;testng&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
<row Id="9086" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="2092" CreationDate="2008-08-12T17:58:25.630" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;You can also get the source from a Open Source code coverage tool and learn from it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerDisplayName="Miguel Ping" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T17:58:25.630" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9137" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="9044" CreationDate="2008-08-12T19:03:22.737" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure how the annotation inheritance works for TestNG but this article may be of some use. &lt;a href=&quot;http://beust.com/weblog/archives/000170.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://beust.com/weblog/archives/000170.html&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Actually, this may help better &lt;a href=&quot;http://testng.org/doc/documentation-main.html#annotations&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://testng.org/doc/documentation-main.html#annotations&lt;/a&gt;, look at inheritGroups.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="782" OwnerDisplayName="Sam Merrell" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T19:03:22.737" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9245" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8569" CreationDate="2008-08-12T21:11:13.243" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;Start here - I actually think it's among the best Software Dev books that I've read.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=L7d0LNpSrRwC&amp;amp;dq=expert+spring+mvc+and+web+flow&amp;amp;pg=PP1&amp;amp;ots=GC7894yug6&amp;amp;sig=xndzQdG2YWy27Ffx6kR1rXQwxf0&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;oi=book_result&amp;amp;resnum=1&amp;amp;ct=result&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Expert Spring MVC And Web Flow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Learn the new Annotation-based configuration for MVC classes. This is part of Spring 2.5. Using Annotation-based classes is going to make writing Unit tests a heck of a lot easier. Also being able to cut down on the amount of XML is a good thing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah Unit Tests - if you're using Spring, you BETTER be Unit Testing. :) Write Unit tests for all of your Web and Service Layer classes. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Read up on Domain Driven Design. The fact that you can use Domain Object classes at all levels of a Spring Application means you're going to have a VERY powerful Domain Model. Leverage it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, when using your Domain Object classes for form population, you will want to take heed of the recent security concerns around the Spring Framework. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.theserverside.com/news/thread.tss?thread_id=50076&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;A discussion on the Server Side&lt;/a&gt; reveals the way to close the hole in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="543" OwnerDisplayName="bpapa" LastEditorUserId="543" LastEditorDisplayName="bpapa" LastEditDate="2008-08-12T23:49:30.553" LastActivityDate="2008-08-12T23:49:30.553" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9361" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="16650" CreationDate="2008-08-13T00:49:17.360" Score="3" ViewCount="1541" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'd like to utilize an ICE Faces fileInput control to fill in the file path &amp;amp; file name for the input to an input field on a web page based on file that the user selects. How can I capture these properties without actually performing any file transfer operations?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="318" OwnerDisplayName="KG" LastActivityDate="2009-05-06T03:11:40.483" Title="ICE Faces fileInput file path and file name properties" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;ajax&gt;&lt;jsf&gt;&lt;icefaces&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9404" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8968" CreationDate="2008-08-13T02:02:38.537" Score="3" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you only need some simple process orchestration, Spring's own &lt;a href=&quot;http://springframework.org/webflow&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Web Flow&lt;/a&gt;, despite its name can serve as a orchestration task manager.   If you need to preserve state for several days then you will need to become an 'early adopter' of one of the open-source projects.  You may want to look at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.eclipse.org/bpel/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Eclipse's BPEL project&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My hunch is that once a clearer picture of the BPEL/BPM/Workflow space emerges you will see Spring provide an abstraction layer the same way they have for JDBC, Transactions, ORM frameworks etc... &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="700" OwnerDisplayName="Brian" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T02:02:38.537" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9408" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8219" CreationDate="2008-08-13T02:13:56.410" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;There's also &lt;a href=&quot;https://parallel-junit.java.net/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;parallel-junit&lt;/a&gt;. Depending on how you currently execute your tests its convenience may vary - the idea is just to multithread on a single system that has multiple cores. I've played with it briefly, but it's a change from how we currently run our tests. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://java.net/projects/hudson/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;Hudson&lt;/a&gt;, the continuous integration engine I use, also has some ways to distribute test running (separate jobs aggregated results in one).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="235" OwnerDisplayName="Joshua McKinnon" LastEditorUserId="1102512" LastEditDate="2013-11-26T03:58:10.860" LastActivityDate="2013-11-26T03:58:10.860" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9652" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6765" CreationDate="2008-08-13T11:11:09.460" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;We've been running an application using Hibernate talking to multiple remote MSQL Server instances for a few years now and we also switched to the jTDS driver early on after a few issues with the M$ driver. Since the switch we haven't had any issues at all. However, it's not a complicated application so it doesn't use any LOB's. Hope that helps.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1126" OwnerDisplayName="TiGz" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T11:11:09.460" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9698" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8968" CreationDate="2008-08-13T12:15:19.377" Score="0" Body="&lt;p&gt;We're looking at Drools/Guvnor, possibly integrated with jBPM (as in this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.firstpartners.net/blog/technology/java/2008/06/05/jboss-business-rules-and-jbpm-workflow-presentation-dublin/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;presentation&lt;/a&gt;), to add a workflow engine to our Spring/Java EE app, but we're still in the very early phases of trying it out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="765" OwnerDisplayName="Nicholas Trandem" LastEditorUserId="472792" LastEditDate="2013-08-18T09:19:43.010" LastActivityDate="2013-08-18T09:19:43.010" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9725" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="3049" CreationDate="2008-08-13T12:44:34.937" Score="7" Body="&lt;p&gt;For C/C++ on Windows you have (at least) two choices:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the SerialPort class provided by .NET.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the Win32 API. There is an &lt;a href=&quot;http://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/library/ms810467.aspx&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;extensive MSDN article&lt;/a&gt; dating back to 1995, and many free libraries and examples on the web to get you started.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The .NET option will be much easier.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1077" OwnerDisplayName="Simon Hardy" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T12:44:34.937" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="9743" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6765" CreationDate="2008-08-13T12:56:57.203" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;jTDS is excellent. I've been using it for years without issue in high-availability production environments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="1174" OwnerDisplayName="Olly" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T12:56:57.203" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="10042" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="25311" CreationDate="2008-08-13T16:29:22.063" Score="113" ViewCount="356011" Body="&lt;p&gt;What's the best way to make a linked list in Java?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="571" OwnerDisplayName="Lance Fisher" LastEditorUserId="5432257" LastEditorDisplayName="Kamikaze Mercenary" LastEditDate="2015-10-12T04:40:40.970" LastActivityDate="2015-10-12T04:40:40.970" Title="How do I create a Linked List Data Structure in Java?" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;data-structures&gt;&lt;linked-list&gt;" AnswerCount="6" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="67" ClosedDate="2012-01-03T20:21:00.337" />
<row Id="10050" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10042" CreationDate="2008-08-13T16:35:02.990" Score="53" Body="&lt;p&gt;Java has a &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/j2se/1.5.0/docs/api/java/util/LinkedList.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;LinkedList&lt;/a&gt; implementation, that you might wanna check out. You can download the JDK and it's sources at &lt;a href=&quot;http://java.sun.com/javase/downloads/index.jsp&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;java.sun.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" OwnerDisplayName="david" LastActivityDate="2008-08-13T16:35:02.990" CommentCount="4" />
<row Id="10506" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="10549" CreationDate="2008-08-13T23:57:01.567" Score="2" ViewCount="1420" Body="&lt;p&gt;I am having a strange DB2 issue when I run DBUnit tests.  My DBUnit tests are highly customized, but I don't think it is the issue.  When I run the tests, I get a failure: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;SQLCODE: -1084, SQLSTATE: 57019&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www1.columbia.edu/sec/acis/db2/db2m0/sql1000.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;which translates to&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;SQL1084C Shared memory segments cannot be allocated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It sounds like a weird memory issue, though here's the big strange thing.  If I ssh to the test database server, then go in to db2 and do &quot;connect to MY_DB&quot;, the tests start succeeding!  This seems to have no relation to the supposed memory error that is being reported.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have 2 tests, and the first one actually succeeds, the second one is the one that fails.  However, it fails in the DBUnit setup code, when it is obtaining the connection to the DB server to load my xml dataset.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any ideas what might be going on?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastEditorUserId="1227152" LastEditDate="2016-07-22T20:12:29.757" LastActivityDate="2016-07-22T20:12:29.757" Title="Weird DB2 issue with DBUnit" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;db2&gt;&lt;dbunit&gt;&lt;db2-luw&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="10549" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10506" CreationDate="2008-08-14T01:05:31.087" Score="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, I think I fixed it by doing the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;db2stop force&#xA;db2start&#xA;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At least, things seem to be working now.....&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="122" OwnerDisplayName="Mike Stone" LastActivityDate="2008-08-14T01:05:31.087" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="10586" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="10713" CreationDate="2008-08-14T02:22:37.920" Score="6" ViewCount="3729" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm currently trying to read in an XML file, make some minor changes (alter the value of some attributes), and write it back out again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have intended to use a StAX parser (&lt;code&gt;javax.xml.stream.XMLStreamReader&lt;/code&gt;) to read in each event, see if it was one I wanted to change, and then pass it straight on to the StAX writer (&lt;code&gt;javax.xml.stream.XMLStreamReader&lt;/code&gt;) if no changes were required.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that doesn't look to be so simple - The writer has no way to take an event type and a parser object, only methods like &lt;code&gt;writeAttribute&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;writeStartElement&lt;/code&gt;. Obviously I could write a big switch statement with a case for every possible type of element which can occur in an XML document, and just write it back out again, but it seems like a lot of trouble for something which seems like it should be simple.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there something I'm missing that makes it easy to write out a very similar XML document to the one you read in with StAX?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="797" OwnerDisplayName="Matt Sheppard" LastEditorUserId="1332690" LastEditorDisplayName="Derek Park" LastEditDate="2012-04-25T16:36:06.310" LastActivityDate="2016-04-26T20:30:44.637" Title="Small modification to an XML document using StAX" Tags="&lt;java&gt;&lt;xml&gt;&lt;stax&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="0" FavoriteCount="2" />
<row Id="10660" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10586" CreationDate="2008-08-14T04:13:24.717" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;After a bit of mucking around, the answer seems to be to use the Event reader/writer versions rather than the Stream versions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(i.e. javax.xml.stream.XMLEventReader and javax.xml.stream.XMLEventWriter)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;See also &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.devx.com/tips/Tip/37795&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noreferrer&quot;&gt;http://www.devx.com/tips/Tip/37795&lt;/a&gt;, which is what finally got me moving.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="797" OwnerDisplayName="Matt Sheppard" LastActivityDate="2008-08-14T04:13:24.717" CommentCount="0" />
<row Id="10713" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10586" CreationDate="2008-08-14T05:52:27.730" Score="2" Body="&lt;p&gt;StAX works pretty well and is very fast. I used it in a project to parse XML files which are up to 20MB. I don't have a thorough analysis, but it was definitely faster than SAX. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for your question: The difference between streaming and event-handling, AFAIK is control. With the streaming API you can walk through your document step by step and get the contents you want. Whereas the event-based API you can only handle what you are interested in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="198" OwnerDisplayName="david" LastActivityDate="2008-08-14T05:52:27.730" CommentCount="0" />
